Heat. Heat. N.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
[music] Heat.
Heat.
>> [music]
>> Hey, hey, hey.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat. [music]
[music]
Oh,
hey. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> We must stop the terror. Now watch this
drive.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. [music]
Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Welcome to the Young Turks. Janker
Anakasparing with you guys. Hell of a
show for you guys tonight. uh really
interesting developments that you uh
might not have heard in the Graham
Platner story and the Mitch McConnell
story. Is he even alive? I mean, what an
amazing
uh circumstance that we find ourselves
in where uh we can't trust anyone in
government or anyone in media. And we
have to wonder whether prominent
senators are even alive. Okay.
[laughter]
And speaking of people who are alive or
or not, uh unfortunately we do have
tragic news in that the war has
restarted. We're going to get to that in
a second. But also on tonight's show,
John Keryaku, former CIA officer, will
join us. That should be a very
interesting interview. He apparently
thinks that I [snorts] hate him. Um, as
far as I know, that's not true. So,
buckle up. Fascinating uh interview
today. How you feeling, Casper?
>> I'm feeling okay. I'm feeling okay. It's
my LA I have a little bit of senioritis,
meaning it's my last day before I go
away for a week. So, let's get the show
on the road.
>> Let's do it. You crazy. All right, let's
go to the first story.
So, what you're watching here is uh
footage of US strikes uh on Iran that
were carried out on July 8th. Uh by the
time we're going live now, uh the US has
struck Iran
170 times in the last uh two days. So,
the war is definitively back on. Uh and
Iran is also striking us in Jordan and
uh many other countries where we have
bases and uh of course uh the Israelis
are thrilled about what's happening.
More war. They're psyched that obviously
it's a disaster for us Iran and the rest
of the world. Anna has more facts.
>> I sure do. And in fact, Israel isn't
satisfied with simply
going to war with Iran and having
multiple theaters of war in the Middle
East. Uh they're of course still talking
about the likelihood of going to war
against Turkey, but let's focus on Iran
for the purposes of this discussion
because there was some confusion today
following strikes that were seen in
Chabahar uh in southern Iran. And at
first the thinking was, well, the United
States has reignited this war, so those
are US strikes. But it turns out that
the United States came out and said,
actually, no, those were not our
strikes. Then Israeli media uh confirmed
that these bombings were carried out by
Kuwait and Bahrain, meaning that some of
our uh Gulf allies have decided to
retaliate against Iran, even though Iran
has been striking US military bases
inside these countries. There were also
some strikes in Abbas, which is um the
capital of Iran's oil producing
province. And so the strikes that have
been carried out by the United States
this time around appear to be a little
more strategic than the seemingly
indiscriminate bombing the US was
engaged in at the very beginning of this
war. As for Israel, uh Drop Site News is
reporting that Israeli Prime Minister
Benjamin Netanyahu said the war with
Iran is quote not over. While Defense
Minister Israel Katz said Israel is
prepared to strike Iran again with even
greater force if it deems it necessary.
Kat said the Israeli military is
prepared to resume fighting to regain
air superiority and strike Iran again,
including a third time if necessary,
adding the campaign is not over. Now,
uh, it's unclear if or more importantly
when Iran will retaliate against Israel
because Israel is the whole reason why
this war started in the first place. But
so far, it doesn't appear that uh Iran
has taken any hits at at Israel. Now, US
Central Command said late night on
Wednesday that uh on Wednesday, they had
struck about 90 military targets to
further degrade Iran's ability to attack
commercial shipping in the street of
Hormuse. In fact, if you see the
locations of the various US strikes,
it's very clear that these strikes are
intended to, you know, weaken Iran's
capability in attacking commercial
vessels. Iran's health ministry said at
least 14 people were killed and almost
80 people were injured uh over the first
two days of the US strikes. So, I'm sure
that death toll is probably going to uh
increase in the coming days. Now, Iran
said that it did hit back with uh
missile and drone strikes targeting US
military bases in Kuwait, Bahrain, and
Qatar. Iran says that the US targeted
railway bridges um on the route to the
holy city of Mashad where of course the
late supreme leader was due to be buried
buried and he did you know they did
continue on after a short delay uh with
the ceremonies. Uh but Iran's foreign
ministry said that the attacks while
Kam's 6-day funeral procession was
underway signified Washington's
inability to comprehend the depth of
Iranians patriotism and loyalty to the
revolution's ideals. And and I should
just say I mean if anything what we have
accomplished through this war jank is
really getting the Iranians to rally
around the flag because if you look at
the footage of the various events having
to do with Kam's uh funeral you'll
notice that there are now tens of
millions of people out on the streets.
[snorts] Now, additionally, a railway
bridge in the town of Akala in the
northeastern Golastthan province was hit
with cruise missiles, and that's
according to Iran's revolutionary guards
who said there were no casualties. The
line plays an important role in transit
and trade with uh central Asia and is
part of an international corridor that
links Iran, Turkmanistan, and
Kazakhstan. So again kind of providing
more reinforcement to the notion that
the US is striking you know economic
infrastructure and it does look like
these strikes are more strategic. A
tanbased businessman in fact told the
Financial Times the following that the
rail line had been used um while uh the
US was engaging in blockades of Iranian
ports. He said when the blockade was on
people would use it yet it has very
limited capacity. Each train uh from
China uh Shien in China would only carry
about 3,800 tons. But attacks were also
reported on electricity infrastructure
in Chabahar and uh Canar in southeast
Iran causing three electricity
transmission lines to go out of service
and cutting off power to parts of the
region. Now, um, if anyone is hoping
that maybe things will kind of calm down
a little bit and Trump will encourage,
you know, peace negotiators to get back
to negotiating, uh, Ben Shapiro is
making clear that he is vehemently
against it and in fact he thinks it
makes us look weak if we are pursuing
diplomatic means to end this war. He has
a different idea in mind. Let's let's
take a listen.
>> So, what exactly could be done? Well,
first, we could force open the straight.
I know. We haven't even tried it. We
didn't try it. We could do it. We could.
If you think that the US military does
not have contingency plans for opening
the Straight of Hormuz along with our
allies, you're out of your mind. We do.
We just decided we didn't want to cuz we
we got chicken with Saudi. And we were
told by our magical negotiators that a
deal was was in the offing, which was a
lie. It wasn't true.
And we could open the straight. We could
destroy Kar Island, which is their oil
export facility. We could destroy the
South Ps gas field. We could basically
put their economy on unsupportable legs.
We could put the regime into its death
rows. Those are all things that we could
do. Or we could just walk away and let
our allies do any or all of those
things. We could do any of those things.
But here's the thing we should not do.
Demonstrate weakness by going back to
the table and pretending once again that
they are reasonable, rational people.
In order to take control of the straight
of Hormuse, we would need to dedicate I
mean the troop commitment for that type
of operation because it's not just about
snatching control, it's about
maintaining control and we do not have
the troops necessary to make that
happen. Additionally, uh Tom Nichols
over at the Atlantic of all places,
which shocked me, uh has the complete
opposite take from Ben Shapiro. In fact,
he writes uh that the president is still
considering two terrible ideas. First,
he has returned to talking about seizing
Carg Island, an operation that would
require a considerable commitment of
ground forces and inevitably lead to US
casualties. Second, he has again raised
the possibility of striking Iran's
infrastructure, including bridges and
desalination plants. Such installations,
he writes, if they are significantly
contributing to Iran's military effort,
might be considered legitimate targets.
Trump, however, seems to have in mind
emiserating the civilian population as a
means of driving the regime to the
table, which would be a serious
violation of the laws of war. But the
one thing I disagree with Nicholls on in
this analysis, Jenk, is I don't think
the US was ever serious about a peace
deal. I think it was all lies. I think
JD Vance, the vice president, was being
honest when he said, you know, theou was
really about getting the oil flowing
again and basically preparing for more
kinetic warfare against Iran. That's
exactly what happened. That was the plan
from the very beginning. There was never
any real good faith effort at peace
here.
>> Yeah. So, uh, first let's start with
Israel first and Ben Shapiro. Um, so of
course, what does he want? more war. Uh,
and who does he want it from? Us. So, I
I don't know if these uh people are
still even bothering to pretend to be
Americans or care about American
interests. So, that whole segment of
course was you have to do what Israel
wants and Israel always wants more war.
But of course, we are the victims and we
are doing self-defense. What does Iran
have to do with self-defense?
Nothing. It doesn't matter. It doesn't
matter. The Israelis have ordered war
and we have more war. And every time in
the media they will tell you, "Oh, it's
just a coincidence. Just a total and
utter coincidence that we do exactly
what Israel wants nearly 100% of the
time." Oh, hey, look, it's 98%. We sold
some planes to Turkey that they didn't
want. Oh, see that? You have 2% freedom
left. Congratulations Americans.
[snorts] Uh, but of course, no one else
points out that Ben Shapiro, Mark Levin,
Laura Loomer never argue for American
interests. They always pretend that
American interests are identical to
Israel's interests. Very coincidentally,
no two allies have identical interests.
And Israel and America have nothing uh
that is similar here. We don't like
Hamas and Hezbollah. I I hate to break
it to American media who think Hamas and
Hezbollah are the biggest problems
America faces. They're not anywhere near
us. And outside of Israel, they're not
even our enemies. They have no reason to
be our enemies other than no, you must
all do everything ISRAEL COMMANDS YOU TO
DO. ATTACK your neighbors. Attack their
enemies. No. No. Israel's not Uncle Sam.
And they God damn it, man. So anyway, so
now we're [snorts] back into this
disastrous war. Of course, the question
that Ann asked is the one that
everybody's asking, which is, is this,
you know, uh, back to war permanently or
is this another one of these flare ups?
And then we go back to pretending
there's a ceasefire, more flare-ups, and
it goes on and on and on and and to what
end, right? [snorts]
So, if we want to deal with the
Iranians, we already have the outline
for a deal. Just do the damn deal. Do
the damn deal. Right? But no, no, no,
no. Must must obey. Must kneel to a
foreign government. So, uh, in this
case, there's two different issues. One
is the Omani route, and that's the route
that some of the ships were taking that
Iran has not authorized. So, Iran hits
them on the Omani route. I I don't know
if they should have hit them or not hit
them, that's not my business. Okay? And
so, if you want to be pissed about that
and say that's a violation of the
ceasefire, fine. At the same time, uh,
we we have been violating the ceasefire
non-stop because part of theou is that
Israel must withdraw from Lebanon. And
Israel has already said, "We're never
going to do that. We're going to steal
southern Lebanon for greater Israel."
Right? So, and if you think I'm
exaggerating, no. Israel cats many other
uh ministers in their cabinet and in
Netanyahu said they are not withdrawing.
They're not going to withdraw during the
so-called ceasefire. They're not going
to withdraw afterwards. And very very
very likely based on their statements,
they are never going to withdraw because
this is all about land expansion for an
obviously fascist empire in the middle
of the Middle East with weapons of mass
destruction that is a huge danger to the
world. But this time we're on the
fascist side. And it breaks my heart as
an American. We should not be on the
side of darkness and the ones that are
invading and attacking all of their
neighbors and taking their land. So, but
we have to do all their dirty work for
them because everybody in Washington
says if you don't serve Israel, you're
an anti-semite and you should your life
should be destroyed and pulverized. So,
now uh we've got more people involved in
this war. You know, they hit the
northern railways. So, there's a couple
possibilities as to why it hit the
northern railways. One is the economic
reasons. The other is well, the funeral
procession was going to go in that area
and a lot of the other countries in the
Gulf are Sunni and Iran is Shiite. So
maybe they want to send a message, oh
yeah, we don't respect your grand
Ayatollah. That's the head of the Shiite
uh sect of of Islam. Shiites and Sunnis
have been fighting for literally over a
thousand years. So uh so that could have
something to do with it. Uh but overall
uh we're right back in the soup, right
back in the mess. 170 bombs is an
bombing runs is an enormous amount. That
is not a slight tweak. And so is this
just about the Omani route? And hey, we
get a little bit back and forth and then
cool down for a minute. I mean, I hope
so, but it doesn't look like it because
this is not like the other bombings
during the ceasefires. The other
bombings would be two, three, four
bombs, send a message both Iran and the
US. Iran did the same thing here. Try to
send a message, two, three bombs in the
Omani route uh on ships. And America
said no, 170, right? Let alone uh the
Kuwait, Bahrain, and whoever else bombed
northern Iran. So right now it looks
like full-scale war. Uh you know Trump
is of course a maniac. So he says two
different things at all times. He said
the ceasefire is over and and you know
we're back to war. And then today he
said oh the Iranians called and they're
begging uh to go back to a ceasefire of
that's a total lie. It's corroborated by
zero people. Total imagination fantasy
of a borderline lunatic that's our
president. So, is are is the ceasefire
over or are we about to go back in the
ceasefire? Well, Trump tells you both
things. That's obviously impossible. And
again, he's a raving madman. So, we have
a raving mad man who listens to a
fascist government and none of these
people care 1% about American interests.
So, likely you'll all be forced back
into the war and all the terrible
consequences that flow from that. And
then later, they'll pretend that it had
nothing to do with Israel and oh golly
gee, you know, it's just a coincidence.
that we follow their orders every single
goddamn time.
>> Okay, so a little bit of um background
info that I think is really relevant to
kind of figure out what's going on right
now. Uh the war is on and anyone who's
trying to downplay it by calling it a
military operation or pretending like we
still have a ceasefire is delusional.
Like I'm I'm I think that we have
degraded like people's minds in this
country have been degraded because we've
redefined what it means to be in war.
What we're experiencing right now is a
war. Okay. Iran did not violate anyou.
Okay. They just they didn't theou makes
clear that they will maintain control of
the straight of formoose. Uh the United
States was trying to do some tricky
pizzazziki nonsense of having ships
transit through uh the straight on the
Omani side in order to basically ensure
that Iran cannot establish uh the
approved routes uh for these ships to
travel through. And look, here's the
thing. Trump wants the war to end, but
he doesn't want to accept the fact that
the United States lost. This was a dumb
war, which is why every previous
administration that was being pressured
by Netanyahu to enter this war refused
to do so. Every other administration was
intelligent enough, and we don't have a
lot of intelligent administrations in
this country. Let's just keep it 100.
But they were smart enough to know if we
attack Iran, this is a country that has
a far more superior military capability
than Iraq did. the land mass is larger,
the terrain is more challenging, and
they're going to shut down the straight
of Hormuz. We're not going to do it. But
Trump was stupid enough to do it now.
Why? Well, because he has morons in his
ear who play him like a fiddle. And so,
Alex Ward uh over on X reported the
following. Israel shared new
intelligence with the US that it said
indicated a fresh Iranian plan to kill
President Trump. people familiar with
the matter said Iran for years has vowed
openly to retaliate against Trump for
the assassination of Kasumsulammani.
So basically you have the Israelis in
Trump's ear and Netanyahu has done this
before. You know he did a press tour
where he purported that the Iranians
have a an active plot to assassinate
Trump. Well, he was just in Trump's ear
again. And this is what happens with
Trump. He makes decisions on the fly.
He's unhinged and now we find ourselves
in another war or the war reigniting
and the global economy is going to
crash. Jenk, like that's the big issue
here. Okay. The Iranians, they win
simply by surviving and time is on their
side. Everyone knows that the longer
this war goes on, the longer the
straight of Hormuse is closed, the the
worse it's going to be for the global
economy.
>> Yeah. And
again, you don't just snap your fingers
and it happens. Let's say the war ends
today. It's still going to take months
for things to normalize in the straight,
which is why it was so incredibly
important to end the war immediately.
But no, we're back on. And so Israel,
you're right, ecstatic. They've been
wanting this. Uh but the global
community is going to be furious with
Israel because everyone knows that this
war began thanks to Israel. And uh what
what's Israel going to do? Oh, you guys
are just a bunch of Jew haters. It's not
that we've like destroyed the world with
our blood lust and absolute, you know,
desire for endless conflict.
>> Yeah. So, look, uh I'm done trying to
prevent it. Uh I tried my hardest. We
all tried our hardest. uh and before the
first war, before the second war, before
the reigniting the third uh you know
portion of the war. Uh but
Israel totally controls Washington. Uh
so there's nothing we could do, guys. It
doesn't matter if even if you all voted
against incumbents tomorrow, there's not
enough primaries left. They'd beat
Thomas Massie. So that means that the
Republicans 100% serve Israel. the
Democrats are now panicking a little bit
because they're beginning to lose their
elections uh for serving Israel. Uh but
it's too late. Uh you know, whatever the
consequences are going to be, they're
going it's going to happen. And uh you
know, so just we're occupied and that's
why we're being forced into this war.
And they could cry about it all day
long. I don't care about them at all.
Everybody in Washington is a bunch of
liars uh that constantly try to
manipulate you into believing that we're
not occupied by Israel when it's the
most obvious fact in the world. And and
what are the consequences that's going
to happen to Anna's point is that yeah,
our media can keep trying to brainwash
people like a bunch of obvious like
propagandists,
but our cable news doesn't go to the
rest of the world and the rest of the
world can see things super clearly.
Yeah, there's tons of Israeli propaganda
in some of the European countries and
Western countries as well. Uh but it's
not as thick as it is here and in the
rest of the world, it barely exists. So
no, everybody knows this war is 100% for
Israel. The only people that don't uh
believe that are people who are
brainwashed by our Israeli media in this
country pretending to be American media.
So um so they're all going to be furious
at Israel because the economy is going
to suffer terribly through this war. And
so let's see where the consequences wind
up. And I hate it. I don't want it. I
don't want there to be any consequences.
I don't want there to be any war. But
it's baked in now. It's it's over. And
so, um, and should you be mad at the
people who brought you this war?
Obviously. And then they say, I've now
started seeing on social media, Jenk,
you can't say that the war's
consequences should be laid at the feet
of the people who started the war. So,
they know terrible consequences are
coming and they don't want it blamed on
the people who started, who started it.
American politicians who are
disgustingly corrupt and are traitors to
this country. disgustingly corrupt
American media who's always, "Oh, we'll
learn our lessons from Iraq. Oh, yeah,
but not fake weapon of mass
destruction." Right. Back to fake
weapons of mass destruction. Uh serving
Israel, not having learned. There's no
lessons to learn. They're corrupt. They
work for a different country. It's so
obvious if you're not hypnotized and
brainwashed by American I'm/Israeli
uh media. And so, uh yeah. and of course
Israel. It is definitely definitely
their fault. And when the economy goes
south and when we have more Americans
returning in coffins, yes, you should
definitely be furious at the Israeli
government. They are not our allies. I
believe they are our enemies that have
decided that they are going to take
every dollar and every part of our
military and and they don't care about
our interests at all. But that's why I'm
more angry at American politicians and
media because they're supposed to look
out for their own country. Yeah, they're
a fascist warongering country that is
totally out of control and an obvious
pariah state who have brutalized in a
disgustingly fascist way the
Palestinians for the last 58 years as
every liar in American/Israel
media here in America has told you that
the Palestinians are the terrorists. No,
the Israelis are the terrorists that are
terrorizing the entire planet. And they
brought you this war and when this war
goes disastrously, yes, YOU SHOULD BE
FURIOUS at Israel.
Oh, and then they'll say, "Oh, just
because we murdered all these people and
started terrible wars that destroyed
your life, how dare you CRITICIZE US."
NO, BOW YOUR HEAD TO US. THEY'LL SAY,
"WELL, NO ONE'S BOWING ANYMORE. No one's
bowing anymore to a foreign government
like Israel. You want to get us to try
to us to bow? We won't. We're Americans
and we're proud and we hate our that our
government is captured [laughter] by
this tiny nation. Yes. With tons of
billionaires on their side that are
using that money to totally buy our
media and our Congress. Those are facts,
young Turks. We'll be back with Kiryaku.
Super interesting interview.
All I ask of you going forward is keep
fighting forward. Okay? But we don't
fight with arms and physical and any of
that, right? We fight with love. We
fight with peace. We fight with hope and
belief and faith in one another.
>> And and we do that's right with
knowledge and facts and truth and things
that are real.
>> Objective reality matters. So much of
our audience is scientists, teachers,
engineers, data analysts, people who
believe in objective reality, right? So,
thank you guys for believing in that.
Thank you for believing in hope and
thank you for making it happen. I
appreciate all
[applause]
Y
[groaning]
I really love what y'all do um on the
Young Turks, man. And it's just it's
just it's a very refreshing, you know,
voice. You know, y'all don't lean to one
side. I tell people all the time, this
is if you want to go really hear what's
going on honestly in in in our society,
you should tune in uh to the Young
Turks.
>> Thank you, Charlemagne. We appreciate
that.
>> That's awesome. really appreciate it,
brother. [music]
>> In the bonus episode for members, we do
things that are really productive and
healthy and good for you, like fruit.
I'm just kidding. WE GET THE INSIDE
SCOOP.
>> ICE CREAM CARE. [laughter]
>> COME ON, MAN. Come inside the bonus
episodes and you're going to love it.
Embarrassing details about our lives.
What kind of ice cream we eat?
>> No. Way saucier than that.
>> They're tyt.com/team.
>> Get the inside scoop
ice cream. [laughter]
[music]
>> [music]
>> All right, back on TYT Janana with you
guys. Uh let's go to our interview now.
Joining us now is John Kuryaku. He's a
former CIA officer and a whistleblower
uh who uh uh uh blew the whistle on
torture uh that we were doing inside the
government and has won several awards
including counterterrorism service medal
meritorious honor award, CIA exceptional
performance award, CIA sustained
superior performance award and has a
number of books out. John, welcome to
the show.
>> Thank you so much Shank. You know, you
and I have never had a chance to
actually meet, and you did me a solid
many years ago by talking about my very
first smuggled out letter from prison.
You read it on the air, and I've always
been very appreciative. That's
interesting. Okay, so I saw Look, we're
going to get into super important things
about like who does the CIA actually
work for. Uh, but first, I saw a clip
where you said that I had railed against
you. Do you know where that came from?
Because that never happened. Hold on,
pause because I set this up. Okay, I
came across the clip and I was like,
"Oh, no." But I like John Kuryaku a lot.
Like, what's the beef? So, this is the
clip.
>> What was it?
>> Edit.
>> Okay, this is the moment. Take a look.
>> Hassan Piker's mother mother's maiden
name is Weaguer. And I wondered if he
was related to Chen Weaguer. Michael
Gardner's telling us that he's Chen
Wager's nephew. It's funny. Chank Wager
has never really been a friend of mine
either. The second thing I ever did that
got wide press coverage after blowing
the whistle. Um it was my it was my open
letter to uh to my supporters from
prison. That became my first letter from
Lorettto. That's when Jake Tapper came
to uh to the prison to interview me. Uh
the the the response was universally
positive and interested except for Chank
Wiger. Chen Wiguer just for 30 minutes
just ripped me.
>> And I never understood that because back
then, you know, I I probably agreed on
95% of the issues with Chen Weaguer.
Like, why is he attacking me like this?
But it's just his
>> I I've never been able to draw a bead on
on Chen Weaguer. I mean, I wanted to I I
kind of felt like I should have been
friends with him. He's one of those
guys. It's like an unrequited romance
where you're sort of like you reach out,
you're like, "We should be buds. We
agree about a lot of stuff and then you
know they never call, they never write.
>> Well, it could be required now. So,
John, what in the world [laughter] was
that?
>> I don't know.
>> No, it was a mistaken identity thing
because I became obsessed with figuring
out what it was and I went through our
archives and no such thing exists. So,
it must have been a mistaken identity
and maybe there is a a chank weaguer out
there somewhere who did attack you.
>> Yeah. [laughter] I I I want to apologize
for that because I think I must have
been temporarily insane or something.
That had to be that's what I'm going
with.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, no, don't sweat it. It
mistaken identity. No big deal. Okay,
let's get to serious stuff. So, look,
John, the main thing that I've been
wanting to ask you for a long time is,
do we even have a CIA? Um, so what I
mean by that is the CIA uh seems to let
Israel run wild inside this country. And
so espionage to no end stole our nuclear
secrets, our uranium, our nuclear
triggers, all of our top secrets. And
yet we're like, "Oh, they're our best
allies." And we let them run. And and in
fact, one more, you know, Epstein was
part of uh Iran Contra. And so it's not
like the CIA is not aware of what's
happening here. And so does it exist or
is it just simply the MSAD?
You know, it's it's changed a lot over
the years in that when I first joined
the CIA, we did not like the Israelis at
all. They were spying on us. They made
it clear. They openly spied on us. They
would bring us gifts that had listening
devices embedded in them to the point
where they were not allowed in the
building. we had to rent space to do our
liaison meetings with them because they
just simply were not permitted to come
into the headquarters building. Well,
that that was what 35 years ago. And now
all of a sudden they're being like
embedded with the CIA that there's a
provision in the National Defense
Authorization Act for 2027 that
colllocates them with the the Pentagon
and then allows even closer like five
eyes style liaison with um with the CIA.
And then at the same time, just two
weeks ago, NBC News reported that the
director of DIA, the Defense
Intelligence Agency, had to send out an
all hands email saying that the Israelis
are being unusually aggressive right now
in trying to recruit assets inside DIA,
that all DIA employees need to be extra
careful. So, what are we doing here?
either either the Israelis are ranked as
critical threat for counter
intelligence, which is what they were
when I was there, along with the
Russians, the Chinese, the Cubans, and
the North Koreans,
or were joined at the hip. But it can't
be both.
>> So, here's my follow-up question for for
you on everything that you just said.
What changed? Is it blackmail? like how
did our government and and not just the
CIA, how did our government go from
understanding the risks of being
associated with the Israelis,
understanding that they spy on us,
understanding that while we may say that
they're our allies, in reality they act
like they're our adversaries. So,
>> what changed?
>> Do they have dirt on powerful people in
our government? Or I mean, I'm asking
you to speculate or maybe you know
something we don't know.
>> Yeah. No, they they probably do, but I
think it's I think it's broader and more
nefarious than that in that this is
really a political change. You know, the
the last any Arab leader will tell you
and and many have told me or I've been
in the room when they've told the
American ambassador, the last American
president to give the Arabs a fair shake
was George HW Bush. The last one. They
loved George HW Bush. They loved Kennedy
and they loved Eisenhower. and everybody
else has been a Zionist in terms of
policy. Well, we've had a string of
Zionist [clears throat]
presidents and they just keep the the
Israelis keep chipping away little by
little by little, not just in the White
House, but on Capitol Hill through Apac
and they've gotten us to the point where
if you disagree not just with Israeli
policy, if you disagree with Benjamin
Netanyahu as a person, you are labeled
as anti-Semitic.
of course took them decades to get to
that point, but they did it.
>> Yeah. So, John, more follow-ups here.
So, first of all, on your point about
disagreeing with Netanyahu, uh, only a
third of Jewish Americans agree with
Netanyahu. Twothirds are against them.
So, apparently twothirds of Jews in
America are anti-Semitic by this
ludicrous definition. Ludicrous. And
it's obvious.
>> Can I add something to that?
>> Yeah. because of the party system in uh
in Israel, Benjamin Netanyahu has never
won more than 27% of the vote in Israel.
So, are we supposed to assume then that
73% of Israelis are anti-Semitic?
>> Yeah,
>> it's outrageous.
>> Uh yes, and I could list other uh
historic leaders that did not win a
majority, but one around that number and
then went on to do great damage. Uh so,
okay. Now, our press uh I believe is
mainly is Israeli propaganda. Why do I
say that? Cuz they keep telling us that
things are normal. So, I just want to do
a quick checklist with you to see if
these things are normal. So,
>> they keep saying, "Oh, your our allies
doing espionage to the point where they
are stealing our the most sensitive
technology and intelligence and using it
to build weapons of mass destruction and
doing it over and over and over again is
perfectly normal. Is that really
normal?" No, of course not. And if it
was any other country in the world, we
would be on the brink of war with them
right now.
>> I mean, forget allies, we'd be on the
brink of war with them. Okay. So then
number two, they say, "Oh, to merge our
militaries, as you were talking about
section 219 and the technology and so
that they could take one now soon to be
$1.5 trillion of money we're spending on
defense, and they get the entire benefit
of that for free." They say that's all
perfectly normal. We constantly are
merging our militaries with allies. Is
that normal?
>> We're merging our militaries with the
closest allies that we have in the
world. Very specifically the British,
the Canadians, the Australians, and the
New Zealanders. You know, we've got good
relations with the rest of the the
members of NATO, as one example. Israel
is not in NATO. We have close relations
with most European Union countries.
Israel is not a member of the European
Union. And then just a couple of weeks
ago, the Israeli Defense Minister said
publicly in a in an interview that
Israel's next war would be against
Turkey. Well, guess what? Turkeykey's a
member of NATO. And if there were to be
hostilities between Israel and Turkey,
and Turkey invoked Article 5 of the of
the NATO charter, an attack on one is an
attack on all. the United States would
have to go to war with Israel to defend
Turkey. Is the United States going to go
to war with Israel? Of course not. And
so what happens? The Israelis then
successfully destroy NATO. Is that
really the the road we want to go down?
>> Not normal. Last one. Last one. Go. Go
ahead. Yeah. So, uh, dozens of Israeli
spies were arrested after 9/11. I'm not
asking about why they were arrested or
what they did, but they were arrested
and they were definitively Israeli
spies. And then we just let them go
free. Yes. Is that normal?
>> Yes,
>> that actually is normal.
>> Nor normal. Normally if let's say an
American spy gets caught in a friendly
country, you know, publicly we deny deny
deny that this person is a spy. We deny
and then secretly quietly we go to the
the station chief will go to the head of
the service and say, "Listen, he's my
guy. You busted us. Do me a favor here
and just let him go." and then quietly
they'll let him go. They may make him
cool his heels for a week or two, but
eventually they're going to let him go.
The reason why I I'm speculating here. I
believe that the reason why there were
so many Israeli spies arrested in New
York in the days after 9/11 is that the
Israelis had advanced warning of 9/11
and didn't tell us. And that was a
policy decision. We asked every ally in
the world. We begged them if they had
any sources inside al-Qaeda, please help
us because we knew this massive attack
was coming, but we didn't know when and
where. We knew it was going to be giant.
We just didn't know when and where. I
believe that the Israelis did know that
they had infiltrated al-Qaeda, but they
didn't tell us because they wanted us to
attack al-Qaeda. They knew that if we
were attacked that we would overreact
like we did. We would launch a war that
lasted 20 years. We would kill 2 million
Muslims, which we did, and spend
something like $6 something trillion
dollar on national defense. You know,
just like they knew chaos in Iraq was
good for Israel, chaos in Libya was good
for Israel, chaos in Syria was good for
Israel, and now chaos in Iran is good
for Israel. It hasn't changed since
9/11.
>> Cancer on our globe. Honestly, I it's
So, you just said something very
provocative. Uh something that I alluded
to in one post on X once. Uh and I
didn't even allude to it as aggressively
as you just did. I just noted the, you
know, five Israelis who got arrested
because they were seen celebrating the
World Trade Center getting attacked. Um,
and I was like, whatever happened with
this? Like, what is this? And there is
evidence that the Israelis had
fornowledge. So, can you can you get
into that a little bit because I think
it's important for members of our
audience who might not know what that
evidence is and why so many people um
have believed that the Israelis had
fornowledge.
>> Yeah. Dozens of Israelis were were
Israeli citizens were arrested uh by
NYPD officers on September 11th and in
the days after September 11th, mostly
for photography, for taking pictures of
sensitive sites, taking pictures of the
uh World Trade Center, things like that,
or making comments uh about the the
attacks. And so they were picked up and
they were held on suspicion of, you
know, something national security
related. And finally the Israelis came
to us and said, "Listen, these are our
guys. Just let them go." Right? They're
they're worried about you. They were
worried about the World Trade Center.
They didn't mean any harm. I think they
were there just to sort of document what
was happening because they knew it was
going to happen. Um,
in in the months before 9/11
>> Mhm.
>> I I was working in the CIA's
counterterrorism center at the time and
um in the months before 9/11, the
leadership of the counterterrorism
center was scrambling. Uh I happened to
be entertaining a group of Middle
Eastern intelligence officers one day.
It was July the 6th, 2001, and Kofheer
Black, the director of the
counterterrorism center, came into my my
meeting, shocked me. I jumped up at
attention and I said, "Oh, gentlemen,
this is Kofer Black. He's the director
of the CIA's counterterrorism center."
And Kofer minced no words. He said,
"Something terrible is going to happen.
We don't know what. We don't know where.
We don't know when, but we know it's
going to be an attack on a massive
scale." And he went into some detail
with them and he said at the end of his
little talk, I'm begging you. He said,
if you have any sources inside al-Qaeda,
please help us. Well, the truth was we
didn't have any sources inside al-Qaeda.
And that's why we needed help from
liaison. But they didn't. The other Arab
countries didn't. The Gulf countries
didn't. The Pakistanis either didn't or
wouldn't tell us. And the Israelis just
sat back and waited for it all to happen
and then came and said, "We are one with
you, America. We are with you." Well,
they knew exactly what was going to
happen. Yeah.
>> And then eight years later, uh, under
Obama, we began arming al-Qaeda
terrorists in Syria.
>> That's exactly right.
>> Yeah,
>> that's exactly right.
>> So, John, I just want to ask one more
followup about that because uh, so I
call this oops, it got past the goalie,
right? So, and and
I like of course our press never talks
about it. They all pretended everything
is a conspiracy theory. Uh I believe
that the phrase conspiracy theory was
actually concocted after the Kennedy
shooting to just call everything that
was that against the official government
position a crazy lunatic thing to
believe. Uh etc. But okay. So, but I
could never square. Well, you know, if
there was a conspiracy and there was did
they really kill all the people on the
planes and how did they get the Arabs to
do the thing that they wanted? Blah blah
blah. And then uh many many many years
later uh in fact after October 7th I
realized, oh, you know, this is actually
potentially easier than I realized. You
just find plots and you probably in
intelligence and that's why I'm asking
you find plots all the time. And if you
want one of them to be successful for
political reasons, you go, "Oh, I just
got past the goalie. There's nothing I
could do." So, is it possible that
October 7th was another one of those?
>> Oh, listen. Call me a conspiracy
theorist, but I think that's exactly
what happened. We know now in retrospect
that for 2 weeks before October 7th,
Israelis who were living in settlements
along the the line, the border with Gaza
were reporting back to uh the Ministry
of uh national security that something
was happening in Gaza. And Idomar
Bengavir said, "No, nothing is happening
in Gaza. The next attack is going to be
in the West Bank." And it was Idomar
Bengavir who ordered that government um
uh what's the word I want to use that
that assets were being used government
assets were being used against you know
possible cells in the West Bank. Well,
there was nothing happening in the West
Bank,
>> right?
>> And and these settlers were saying,
"Look, you know, the the the Gaza
Palestinians are flying kites along the
border. They're releasing balloons.
They're checking wind speeds. their
their chatter uh on the walkie-talkies.
No, you're wrong. It's going to be in
the West Bank. So, I think boy, I really
like that, you know, slip by the goalie.
I think I might steal that because I
think that is exactly what happened.
>> Yeah. I mean, and the fact that it took
six hours for the IDF to respond. And
you know, just fast forwarding to the
moment that we're in now, I just can't
get over the incredibly weak and
pathetic arguments that are being made
by individuals who have been corrupted
with money from the Israel lobby,
essentially arguing that we must merge
our militaries because the IDF, I mean,
how could we give up this opportunity uh
to take advantage of their expertise and
their superior operations? They took six
hours to respond to October 7th
>> and then killed the Israelis
>> and then killed their ownact that were
in cars trying to evacuate the area.
Yeah. You know, one one thing that that
most mainstream outlets don't talk about
is that the Israelis are already in the
United States training local police
departments. We know, for example, that
the Israelis are training the Atlanta
police. that this area now called Cop
City is the site of Israeli police and
Israeli IDF training our own police. I
don't want the Israelis training
American police departments. The
Israelis have no respect for human
rights or civil rights or civil
liberties. And so, look, this is a
country that has that has bombed seven
of its neighbors in the past year.
>> Is that really the country that we want
to throw our lot in with? I would say
no. [clears throat]
>> So, John, uh, Pete Hexath wrote in his
book that the IDF should be in American
streets. So, there's so many Israeli
assets inside our, uh, government that
it's unbelievable. So, okay, which
brings me back to section 219. So, you
mentioned it earlier. It used to be
called section 224, now it's 219 going
into the National Defense Authorization
Act. They tried it with no vote before.
Now, there's more of a, you know,
uprising against it. Of course, as
usual, Roana, Tom Massie leading the
charge against it. And as usual, uh, 94%
of Congress saying, "No, no, no, no. We
serve Israel loyally." So, tell tell us
about the dangers of merging our
technology with with Israel's and why
this should be completely unacceptable
to the American people.
>> You know what, Chank? I'll start I'll
start back from my very first week in
the CIA, January of 1990. uh that first
week you just sit in the auditorium and
you get briefing after briefing after
briefing from you know the director
comes and congratulates you. Then you
hear from the head of HR and the head of
health insurance and the head of life
insurance and the director of security
and the director of security gave us a
couple of you know kind of real life
day-to-day pointers. don't ever eat in
this steakhouse down the street from the
CIA because the KGB thinks we all eat
there and every table is taken by the
KGB, for example. I've never been in
there. But another thing he said, um,
and this is dated, it's 1990, but I
would venture to say that it's worse
today than it was in 1990. He said that
there were two official Israeli
intelligence representatives in
Washington. This was at the Israeli
embassy in Washington. It was uh one
person from Assad and one person from
Shinbet. Okay. And they carry out
liaison. But the FBI was able to
identify
187 Israeli spies spread out all across
America,
mostly infiltrating American defense
contractors to steal our secrets. It
didn't end with the arrest of Jonathan
Pard. and he said Israel is critical
threat for counter inelligence along
with Russia, China, Cuba and North
Korea. And I think Iran may have been on
the list at the time too. Um, and
Israel. And I'll give you another
example. When we came up with this
ill-advised F-35,
the Israelis came to us first and said,
"We want the F-35." And we said, "Great.
We're going to give you the F35. We're
going to slightly degrade the avionics
because, god forbid one gets shot down
and the Russians or the Chinese, you
know, get it in Syria or Iran or
whatever. So, we're going to call it the
F-35I. I I for Israel. The Israelis
said, "No, we want your F-35. We don't
want any I with degraded avionics." At
the same time, the Emiratis came to us
and they said, "We want this new F-35."
And we said, "Great. will give you the
F-35 with slightly degraded avionics
because, god forbid, one should be shot
down and the Russians or the Chinese,
the Iranians get it. We're going to call
it the F-35E for Emirates. The Emirates
gladly took the F-35E.
The Israelis sent their spies all over
the defense sector to steal the avionics
so that when they finally got the F-35i,
they could upgrade them on their own.
And that's the country that we want side
by side with our people in the Pentagon
and the CIA and god forbid NSA or DIA
when the director of DIA is warning
every single employee that they are
unusually aggressive against us right
now, the Israeli Mossad.
>> Yeah.
>> And that people have to be extra
careful.
>> So that brings me back to the what we
started with, John, which is I I is the
CIA still American? uh because they
don't act like it. And and so all this
espionage is going on. It's super
obvious that it's the Israelis and it
doesn't seem like we're doing a damn
thing about it. We're just letting them
run wild in this country. And I want to
go back to to Epstein because we know
that Epstein was part of Iran Contra. He
helped clean seemingly with MSAD. And
let let's you know, I'll let you talk
about what you know how much you know
about that, right? But but also Okay. So
the CIA at that moment knows Epstein
seems to be with Israeli intelligence
because we just did a deal with him. We
just did a deal with him. Then they let
Epstein rape girls in this country for
decades afterwards. So is the CIA
working for America or for Israel?
>> You know, I hate to say this, but I the
only conclusion that I can draw is that
it's working for Israel. You know, when
you've got the likes of Mike Pompeo at
the CIA who was one of the the foremost
Zionists on Capitol Hill. Um, and he and
he's guiding policy. Remember, the CIA
is a policy support organization. It's
not a policy organization. It's supposed
to do what the president tells it to do.
But historically, it had pushed back
against Israel. And then you get Mike
Pompeo in there who might as well be the
head of Mossad for for his uh support of
Israel, everything begins to change. And
when and when you have this constant
pressure from Capitol Hill where
practically everybody is taking money
from Apac
and um and and are they're primared if
they don't take money from Apac or if
they don't tow the line that Apac sets
then you know you lose that independence
and the next thing you know you are
working for the Israelis. Oh
>> god. So how do you see this ending?
Because we don't live in a sovereign
country under what you just described.
we don't live in a sovereign country and
um it fills me with rage and I imagine
it fills a lot of Americans with rage.
So how does this come to an end?
>> Because eventually American citizens are
going to have enough of this.
>> Yeah.
>> Um so how do you see this playing out?
>> In one of two ways really. On the one
hand, I I've long been accused of being
irrationally optimistic about life, and
the the optimist in me says, "Well,
certainly our elected leaders will come
to their senses eventually." But I've
got to be realistic. And I I just don't
think that's going to happen.
>> I don't think that they'll come to their
senses because well, for a couple of
reasons. Number one, because if you look
at the incremental change over the LA or
changes over the last 35 years, every
one of those changes has been in support
of Israel.
>> Yep.
>> Number one. Number two,
even though public opinion polls are
showing that now a clear majority of
Americans uh believe that our
relationship with Israel is too close,
believe that Israel is committing a
genocide in in Gaza, believe that Israel
is the aggressor uh in in all of these
recent conflicts, our elected officials
still line right up in support of
Israel. And you've got people like
Thomas Massie and Ro Kana and a small
handful of others, Marjgerie Taylor
Green who's now gone, but a small number
willing to stand up, that number doesn't
really grow. So even if let's say 77% of
Democrats pled say they support the
Palestinian side in this conflict,
90% of elected Democrats support the
Israelis. And where does that leave us?
That leaves us in a place where we don't
have a democracy.
>> Yeah, we are an occupied country. So,
okay, I now have a random question for
you that I've been meaning to ask for a
long time. So, I want to make sure I get
it in here. So, uh Barack Obama did
something unacceptable uh when he bombed
Anoir Alaki. Uh he he went outside of
the judiciary and he said due process
does not have to be judicial process.
the executive branch can just decide to
execute an American citizen. Uh, and
they did. But that was already egregious
enough, but they say coincidentally in a
second and completely different bombing,
they also killed Alby's 16-year-old son.
And then coincidentally in a third
bombing, they killed his 8-year-old
daughter. So, were those coincidences or
I have a theory on this one. I'm curious
what you think that maybe Anoir Albaki
was working with the CIA, but then he
flipped on him and so he knew things
that the CIA didn't want out and so they
were wanted to cover all their bases on
anyone who might have known.
I think that's entirely plausible. I'll
tell you, I was one of a very small
handful of CIA officers who had actually
met Anoir Alaki. I met him when he was
the imam of the of the mosque in false
church, Virginia. My Arabic teacher, uh
CIA employee, Arabic teacher took us
there uh so we could learn some of the
uh the vocabulary words associated with
Islam. And um he gave us a tour of the
mosque. He took us to the uh Arabic
language bookstore and then we went to
lunch with him. In 2011, I went to Yemen
to do a study. I was the senior
investigator on the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee at the time working
for John Kerry. And I went to Yemen and
my first meeting on that trip was with
the uh the legal attaches, the FBI
representative in the American embassy.
And I made a joke about, you know, what
are you doing sitting here in your
office? You should be out looking for
Anoir Alaki.
And he said, "We know where Anoir Alaki
is within 3 ft 24 hours a day." And I
stupidly said, "So why don't you arrest
him?"
>> Mhm.
>> Well, because there was never any
intention of of arresting him.
>> The intent was to to kill him, to track
him, and to kill him. That was a policy
decision that was made. But why did we
let him
go as far as he did? I think you're on
to something here. I think he was
probably
a CIA asset at one time. Remember, he
was an American citizen. He was born in
Albuquerque, New Mexico. His father was
the Yemen ambassador to the United
States at the time and and then went on
to become the Yemen Minister of
Agriculture. And um and I think that he
self-radicalized after a while and they
just decided to take him out
at a time and place of their choosing.
May I add one other thing, Ch? You
raised something that's very important.
It's something I've been yelling about
for years.
We murdered him without ever charging
him with a crime.
>> He had a constitutional right to face
his accusers in a court of law and to be
judged by a jury of his peers. And we
murdered him in cold blood. He had never
been charged with a crime. But then a
week later, we murdered his 16-year-old
son and 16-year-old nephew as they sat
at a cafe drinking tea. They were
children and they had never been charged
with any crime. And then we murdered his
daughter just for good measure, an
8-year-old, which made Obama a child
killer. Of course, he already was a
child killer, but made him a child
killer again. And nobody really seems to
care. What about his rights? Because
remember what Eric Holder told Ran Paul.
If the president wants to kill you, he's
perfectly within his legal rights to
kill you. And it doesn't matter if you
have never been charged with a crime. If
the president of the United States
doesn't like your politics,
he can make you vapor
with a missile.
>> Yeah.
>> We're in super dark times here. Uh I'm
so we got to go. But John, uh, am I
right that your background is Greek
originally?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay. But I want to end, you know, you
say you're an optimist. I'm an optimist.
Uh, the one beautiful thing about this
country is here's a Turk, a Greek, and
an Armenian. All fighting,
>> right? [laughter]
>> And by the way, this is really
important. All
>> John, I got your back.
all all Americans and all fighting not
for Turkey, Greece or Armenia, but for
America as it's supposed [clears throat]
to be. And and so,
>> you know, we we love this country and we
want its sovereignty and its freedom
back. So, thank you for joining us,
John. Really appreciate it.
>> Thank you so much for the invitation. It
was a pleasure.
>> Come back soon.
>> I look forward to it.
>> All right. Okay, guys. When we come
back, uh uh is Mitch McConnell dead?
[laughter] Our mainstream media won't
tell the truth about anything. So, we've
got to dig and dig to find out why won't
they have an election and what actually
happened with the Grand Platner story.
So, a lot more. Come right back.
>> Are you still talking about Jeffrey
Epstein?
>> Rich and powerful men abusing,
assaulting, and abandoning young women.
These rich and powerful men donate to
the politicians in Washington DC, play
golf with the elites in Washington DC.
They are foreign leaders who we don't
want to offend. They interact with our
intelligence agencies that we don't want
to disobey. There is something [music]
rotten in Washington.
>> And are people still talking about this
guy, this creep?
>> All those congressmen you just saw there
are on the record as protecting the
child rapists who were clients of
Epstein. They have not prosecuted a
single person outside of Epstein and
Maxwell.
>> Yep.
>> Not one.
>> Is Trump engaging in this cover up
because he's in the Epstein files?
>> I don't understand why the Jeffrey Epste
would be of interest to anybody. It's
pretty boring stuff.
>> So, as the government keeps telling us,
yeah, there's other people. Yeah, they
raped those girls. So what? We're going
to cover up for them. Why are you guys
so mad? A nation that chooses impunity
for the rich and the powerful at the
expense of our children is a nation that
has lost its moral purpose. Are you on
the side of the people? Are you on the
side of America's [music]
children? Or are you on the side of the
rich and powerful who've had their thumb
on the scales and [music] shafted
Americans for decades?
>> [music]
>> The rest of the news media says you
should not fight for positive change. If
you do, you're not really a reporter or
a journalist because reporters and
journalists don't care what happens. I
don't agree. That's not written
anywhere. That's not a law. It's just a
rule that they invented so that
reporters didn't actually challenge the
people that are in power. Well, we don't
agree with that. We think we should
challenge the people in power. That
that's actually [music] makes you a
better journalist, not a worse one.
Who do you guys use?
>> We have AT&T.
>> And how much do you pay per month?
>> 3.45. And that includes a company
discount.
>> How many people?
>> Five phones.
>> $70 a line, right? I've started a
wireless company called Noble Mobile
that is trying to cut everyone's bills
in half.
>> What would like a family of four cost?
The average Noble mobile user is paying
42 a month, but also they're using their
smartphone 17% less.
>> Okay, how's that work out?
>> We give you $20 back in cash every month
based upon how much data you use or
don't use. You know, when you're doom
scrolling or messing around on your
phone, you're like, "Oh, wait. I'm I'm
actually costing myself money right
now." The goal with Noble Mobile is to
encourage us to look up at our
children's lovely faces like uh touch
grass, appreciate life. A friend of mine
calls these things are rectangles of
sadness. So, we're trying to change that
and improve everyone's relationships
with their phones.
>> It's a very noble cause.
>> Well, thank you, sir. That's what it is.
>> Been on YouTube for 20 years. The
original political partner on YouTube,
The Young Turks. The Young Turks. The
Young Turks.
>> Godfather of independent media.
>> Favorite news [music] platform by far.
Oh, it's not even close. The Young
Turks. It's the largest online news show
in the world.
>> I watched you guys before I had a
channel at all. and I watch Jenk. So
Jen's really the start of it all.
>> Big shout out to Shen from Young Turks.
>> Jenk Uer, founder of TYT, a man who
probably needs no introduction. [music]
>> Uh Jen, so great to talk to you.
>> Great to talk to you, David.
>> Danny, you worked for a long time, man.
>> Anna Kasparian is one of the [music]
most followed and influential
progressive women online.
>> I love Anna.
>> Your presence has been essential for me
to really grow. Do all of you know the
Young Turks?
[cheering] This is why what young Turks
are doing is so important.
>> I've watched you for many years. You are
insightful. I thank you for that.
>> I was going to introduce myself, but it
sounds like you guys might know it.
[music]
[cheering]
>> Chank wealthy Muslim. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> All right, back on TYT Jen and Anna with
you guys, but also Gino from Pittsburgh
and hold that thing. Thank you for
joining through tyt.com/join.
That makes huge difference to us.
tyt.com/join. and all these beautiful
people who join through the join button
on YouTube. OA3474, Charles Rhodess, uh,
HRH Comqueen and Carlan App and Jed
Kuzak, thank you for gifting a
membership on YouTube. Guys, uh, I know
it's going to shock you to know this,
but we are besieged by Israeli
supporters here. And if ever there was a
time to help the Young Turks, it is now.
So, if you can do a donation or become a
member through tyt.com/join, that makes
a big difference. Or hit the join button
below on YouTube. All right. Uh let's go
to the next story.
>> We believe that for the movement to to
continue,
>> it can't be made.
And for that reason,
we are suspending campaign operations.
That was Graham Platner suspending his
campaign in Maine. But did he uh because
there's a big question as to whether his
name is going to stay on the ballot or
not. Uh and what actually happened with
Graham Platner. You're going to hear
some developments here that you probably
have not heard elsewhere that are an
amazing and important additions to the
latest story about Graham Platner. And
then what in the world are we going to
do next? So a lot to discuss here. Anna,
tell us all about it.
>> Yes. Well, uh, for those who might have
missed the story, uh, let me just give
you a little context and I'll give you
the latest developments. Now, his
decision to drop out of the race, of
course, has to do with the Politico
article that came out recently where a
woman by the name of Jenny Rascott had
accused Platner of forcibly raping her
in her own home. Now the political piece
omitted some details and uh apparently
there's this uh assumption that the
American people don't need to know about
certain details. You know that Politico
gets to decide which text exchanges they
share with us and we'll get to that in
just a minute. But the way the piece was
written made it seem as though uh or
made the reader believe that you know
Platner like broke into her home and
then forcibly raped her. The
allegations, in my opinion, and not even
in my opinion, based on what we have in
front of us, lack concrete evidence that
he carried out a serious crime of rape.
Uh, Barasicott had deleted all
communications that she had with Platner
in the wake of the alleged assault.
Politico cites the following as
corroborating evidence. uh Facebook
messages that she shared with a friend
where Razakott uh describes Platner as
consensually careless and then proceeds
to spend most of her time complaining
about how she thinks she he might have
slept with a lot of women. Uh a
disclosure to another friend whom she
spoke to about the incident at the start
of Platner's campaign, a man that she
dated after Platner who said that she
had divulged uh bits and pieces of what
had allegedly happened. Um,
and then it wasn't until 2023 when she
disclosed the whole story and recent
emails between herself and her therapist
where she contemplated going to the
press about the incident to which the
therapist, who opted out of providing a
statement or comment to Politico, said
that she would not have to go public
about a traumatic experience in order to
be believed. Now, uh, Rascott was
connected, uh, to Politico through a
woman by the name of Cheyenne Hunt, and
that's a 29-year-old, uh, attorney and
former Platner supporter who founded an
organization known as Reckoning Action.
It's a nonprofit, uh, that focuses on
combating workplace misogyny. So, the
revelations about Platner's uh, alleged
assault, alleged forcible rape is what
eventually did him in. he decided to
drop out of the race and of course it
was after pretty much everyone who had
endorsed him had reversed their
endorsement and it became clear that
there were growing calls for him to step
aside. So uh I want to just quickly go
into the details that were omitted in
Politico's reporting because the
Politico piece uh had failed to report
something that Rascott had said to uh
Jake Tapper actually in a subsequent
interview. Now, she didn't get detailed
about it, but Drop Site News caught it
and decided to investigate it. So, I'm
going to go to uh what Ryan Grim is, you
know, what he reported on X. Politico
knew at the time of publication
precisely what Jenny Rascott texted to
Graham Platner, but deliberately omitted
it from their article. Uh Rascott,
according to the lead political reporter
on the story, told Platner she needed
her glute massage. She told he told her
that he was coming right over and she
responded by telling him not to do so,
but he came over quickly uh to her home
with the door unlocked and he let
himself in. And then uh Ryan Grim says,
"Whether this detail is important to you
or not, it is a shocking breach of
journalistic ethics by Politico and CNN
not to include it in their coverage."
And I agree with him. You know, that
detail might not change your mind about
however you feel about this story or
this alleged incident, but it is not up
to Politico to decide whether or not we
have the full story or the full context.
We deserve the full context, including
what she had texted him prior to his
decision to show up to her house.
>> Yeah. No, it's not close. So, she says,
"Hey, I need a glute massage."
and they're going out at the time. So, I
need you to massage my butt. He comes
over and then this event happens. Now,
again, to be fair, you could hold on,
hold on, hold on, hold on.
>> You could say, "Hey, you know what? She
changed her mind and said, "Don't come
over." You could say he came over and
she changed her mind then and she has
every right to change her mind. That's
absolutely true. But what is not in
dispute is that Politico
purposely hid that from you to make
Platner look more guilty.
They did that on purpose. They had the
text and they chose not to share that
which is at a bare minimum obviously
relevant to the context of what
happened. So that this is what we've
been telling you all along. Look guys,
if you I I've said this a million times,
not related to this story.
>> [snorts]
>> uh related to every outsider who's ever
run the on the left or the right, what
the press does and it is driven by
people with a ton of money who do not
want those people to win. If you think
that's conspiratorial, you literally
know nothing about politics. It's called
oppo research. Everyone who works in
politics knows it. The press never tells
you that they get spoonfed that oppo
research and that it is almost always
from the incredibly wealthy and powerful
packs and lobbies. And it is almost
always against outsiders, almost never
against insiders. And so in this case,
uh, Matt Stler, which we'll get back to
in a second, listed the top donors for
the main Democrats. And it is filled
with people who are in favor of
corporate packs and especially, of
course, Apac. But Politico doesn't tell
you that either. They don't tell you
where they got the opera research. They
don't tell you why they're hiding
critical facts about the case. And
neither did any of the other outlets
that have attacked and attacked and
attacked and attacked. And so why did
they call every girlfriend Graham
Platner has ever had? That was the New
York Times. They called every girlfriend
Adam Schiff has ever had or Marco Rubio
or Ted Cruz. No. No. Those are good boys
and girls. They serve the powerful. They
serve the donor class. So they are not
to be touched. But if you got someone
who will not serve the donor class, then
the objective reporters go and try to
destroy them on behalf of the rich and
powerful. And as you can see from the
political piece, they don't mind lying
to you. They don't mind shredding their
so-called journalistic practices, which
amazingly Mika Bzinski did a great job
of explaining uh when the political
reporter was on uh Morning Joe the other
day and we showed that to you. So
they're liars. They don't have any
principles. They're not journalists.
Their job is to destroy any outsider
that would challenge power.
>> Yeah. I I don't find these allegations
credible. Sorry. Uh forcible rape is
something that you would want to either
fight or flee from. And just the way she
tells the story, how do you stay in your
house after the man who forcibly raped
you falls asleep? Wouldn't you want to
flee your home? And I know, I know,
Anna, you don't know how you would react
if it happened to you. I would get the f
out of there.
>> You actually would know how you would
react. You You were assaulted once and
and you were furious about it, right?
And I would you have invited that guy
over for a cup of tea? No. Okay. So,
anyways, look, but this is super
important, guys. We don't need to judge
the women involved, and that's their
personal lives, and they have different
interpretations. cuz I don't begrudge
them anything, okay? I care about how
does the media treat the different
candidates and are they being honest
with you guys or are they purposely
targeting people and trying to destroy
them and that's why they dig and dig and
dig and the other guys get a free pass?
What have they uncovered about Susan
Collins? Nothing. Right? Why? Because no
one's trying to uncover anything about
Susan Collins. They're not targeting
her. They only target one side. And by
the way, if he's replaced by a corporate
Democrat, which is what we'll move on to
next, um they won't target that person
either. They only target outsiders who
will not serve power.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, um let's get to some
more details. So, Platner maintains that
the uh allegations are false. Uh he says
that he's totally innocent and that
there was no uh non-consensual sexual
activity. Now, uh he had won a decisive
victory earlier with the uh primary
against Collins. Um so Platner who has
won that had won that primary um
has asked for asurances from the
Democratic party that they will I mean
who cares at this point? Who cares?
We're not going to win anything
electorally. We're just not. We're not.
and the very progressives, the very
leftists who claim that they want real
change in this country immediately run
away at the first sign of controversy.
So it make a decision. Is this like a
cute little like cosplay thing that
we're doing or do you actually want
change? Okay, so if you're By the way, I
didn't even really like Platiner all
that much as a candidate to be honest
with you to be fair. So, I wasn't one of
his viferous defenders, but I don't like
the fact that we're normalizing
just making forcible rape allegations
against someone to destroy their
political candidacy. And then what
happens next? I mean, this wasn't
adjudicated at a court of law. He was
never found guilty of doing anything
wrong. So, but it doesn't matter because
how this plays out, whether he did it or
didn't do it, he looks guilty and this
will follow him around forever for the
rest of his life when he hasn't even
seen a single date in court. How is that
okay?
>> Yeah.
>> How is that okay?
>> And and so uh and by the way, there's
extra layers to it. So, he does that 11
minute thing video where he basically
withdraws from the race. I'll get to the
nuance in a second. And everyone in
media all over cable news is like, "Not
good enough. He should have confessed."
Well, he says he didn't do it. No, he he
should say that he did it, but he thinks
he didn't do it. No, he should say what
we want and he should just punch himself
in the face and he should confess the
things that we've accused him of. Well,
what is it? And then, of course, they
went to now smear everyone who supported
him. That's it. They're all guilty. No,
no, we're not going to do any of that.
Now, let's find out who is guilty. Okay,
I want to go to uh forward to graphics
five and six here. So, Matt Sto,
longtime progressive uh and he got heat
in the same ways that we do uh for
saying that there's nuance in this story
in exactly in in the ways that he said
it has nuance and people LIKE NO YOU
CAN'T DO NUANCE, YOU HAVE TO BE AN idiot
and you have to be binary and you have
to destroy everyone in the
establishment's path. He's like really?
and he explained top main Democratic
party donors in recent years are Reed
Hoffman, Haim Saban, and David Ellison.
David Ellison as in the Trump ally who
fired Steven Cobar and is taking over
Tik Tok, CBS News, and CNN. These names
should mean something. Saban may be the
single most important Apac donor in the
Democratic party. That is definitely
true. He continues to say and another
big donor to the main Democratic party
is the founder of Zinga Mark Pinkis who
said in 2024 an attack on Amazon and his
attack on America it goes beyond big
tech and Wall Street crypto fraudster
Sam Brank Bankman Freed's partner Nishad
Singh at FDX gave $100,000 to the main
Democratic party in 2022. By the way,
Pinkis uh is also an enormous supporter
of Israel. Oh, look at that. All of the
top donors for the main Democrats
are all either corporate pack donors,
but really almost all of them are Apac
donors.
And they hated Graham Platner and they
demanded that the press, the Democratic
Party destroy him. And look at that. In
another wild coincidence, Graham Platner
is destroyed. Okay, so if you still
think these are coincidences, you're not
very bright. You can't Oh. Oh, I wonder
if people spending millions and millions
of dollars against one candidate in an
effort to destroy him and have the
entire media behind them makes a
difference and they don't spend it any
on Susan Gos. By the way, these are the
people on theoretically on the
Democratic side. They destroyed their
own candidate because it's not their
candidate. [clears throat] They don't
care if Democrats win or Republicans
win. They only care if Israel wins. Why
do you think they fund both parties?
This is not rocket science. It is
crystal clear what happened. And so now
uh they're going to have a nominating
convention in Maine, Anna. [snorts] And
uh guess who's going to decide who the
new nominee is? 600 Maine Democratic
insiders, the same people funded by the
Apac uh and corporate pack guys I just
named.
>> Of course.
>> Yeah. So
>> I'm not surprised. Of course. Of course
it played out this way. But we're the
bad guys for questioning the credibility
of these allegations that uh we haven't
seen a shred of concrete evidence to
back up. So we're so we are to believe
that there is a man who forcibly raped a
woman on the loose. Just on the loose.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> And by the way, he is not formally filed
yet. Uh and people are getting antsy
about that. Uh they're like, "You only
got 70% of the vote. You got TO GET OUT
RIGHT NOW." OKAY. and all of them. And
by the way, I totally agree with you. A
lot of people on the left are like, "No,
no, no trial. No, I don't want to hear
any evidence. I don't need the context.
I love and believe Politico and New York
Times. Make sure we destroy our own."
Okay. All right. That's if you want to
go that way. I think it's a terrible
idea. And so, uh, you have to file by
July 13th and they have to pick a new
candidate by July 27th. So, I I don't
know what's going to happen. It's not my
business to to on whether he should drop
out or not drop out. All I know with
absolute certainty is that evil forces
targeted Graham Platner to make sure
that a person who was going to represent
the voters overwhelmingly won the
primary could not represent those
voters. So instead, a bunch of corporate
Democrats will get together funded by
Apac and tell you who your next I was
going to say senator is, but they're not
going to pick the next senator. They're
going to pick the next person who's
going to lose to Susan Collins cuz
they're going to say, you know, nine out
of 10 chance, oh, I am slightly less
Republican than Susan Collins, but I
will serve all the donors loyally, which
is the exact opposite of what Graham
Platner was saying. Forget Graham
Platner. The voters who wanted those
policies and principles
are the ones who should be served by the
so-called representatives in Maine. If
they do not pick someone ideologically
aligned with the person who
overwhelmingly won the primary,
main Democrats are telling you, "We are
going to betray you and we're going to
shive you and we're traitors and we work
for the donors and we don't work for the
voters." But good news, it hasn't
happened yet. So, I hope that doesn't
happen and I hope that they pick someone
aligned with Platner's policies, not his
personal life. Will they? Well, guys,
we're all going to get to find out
together. Are there honest Democrats who
give you a real representative, a real
somebody who's got a shot at winning
that Senate seat and is a populist? Or
are they servants of the wealthy and the
powerful who are going to betray you?
The whole country is going to find out
together.
>> All right, we got to take a break. When
we come back, we'll ask whether or not
Mitch McConnell's dead.
All
>> [music]
>> right. Uh,
here we go. I'm going to read these
blind. Let's go to YouTube members
first. Uh, Jed Kuzzac says, "Uh, Ben
Shapiro's voice always sounds like it's
playing on twice speed." It does. It
really does. I thought it was on twice
speed. You So, you nailed it exactly
right, but it's not. He just talks so
fast um and whiny and annoying, but
that's why he has no viewers left at
all. The only people watching him are
the mainstream media guys are like, "Oh,
tweet this out. He's so important and
relevant. He's m much more
representative of the right-wing voters
than Tucker Carlson or Megan Kelly or
any other right-wing podcaster." YO,
YES, YES, YES, YES. ISRAEL, ISRAEL,
ISRAEL. RIGHT. Bunch of liars in
mainstream media. They don't work for
America at all. Uh Jill Meister says,
"Yank Bang Shapiro from TYT like you're
starting a lawn mower." or I don't even
know what that means, but okay. Germaine
Moore says, "Us and Russia are supposed
to be world powers. Look how long
they've been struggling with these tiny
countries." Uh, well, a tiny country
took over us. And then a bunch of
propagandists for Israel go, "Oh, it's
just a tiny little country of 10 million
people. We have no power. I can't
believe you think we have any power at
all." Uh, I don't know. You have half
the world's billionaires that are
supporting you guys that are radical
lunatic Zionists. You think that maybe
half the world's billionaires could be
relevant? Oh, no, no, no, no.
You're not allowed to say that. I said
it because it's true. [snorts]
>> It's true. Zachary Stal says, "Anna,
that uh you for all that you do to
spread the truth." And they're saying,
"Thank you for that about the idea of
terrorist actions. I'm so proud to be a
part of this community." Zachary, we're
so proud to have you, man. I love this
community. Bud Roland says, "Israelis
will sacrifice everything, anything, for
their fantasy nation." um and to steal
everyone else's land. Uh so that's the
Israeli government. Anyway, we'll be
back.
[music]
All right, back on TYT. Shank Anna RJ
1323 MS, thanks for joining. We
appreciate it. They hit the join button
below the video on YouTube. Uh Pat Riggo
2981, thank you for gifting 20
memberships on YouTube. You are amazing.
We appreciate you deeply. Uh and Alex
Seymour, thank you for joining through
tyt.com/join.
Uh now, let me uh get you a lot more
sleep and make your life a little bit
better. Chili Pad 2.0 and O is one of
our sponsors and uh and they help by
modulating your body temperature which
is actually the most important thing
about getting sleep. Um so the it's a
water-based mattress topper that
actively controls your bed temperature.
You want all the way down to 55 degrees,
you could do that all the way up to
115°, no problem. Okay, so you get the
whole range and you don't need a new
mattress. You don't need any
renovations. It actively cools using
just water. The fans push the air
around. Water actually cools you off.
Pulls the heat away from your body.
Precise consistent comfort. And the new
nightstand remote senses when you get
into bed and kicks on automatically.
Dual zones means you and your partner
each set your own temperature. No
subscription needed. You get a 2-year
warranty and they're designed and
assembled here in the USA. So visit
www.sle.me/tyt
to get up to $255
off your Chilad 2.0 know with code TYT.
That's www.sle
p.me/tyt.
Free shipping, free returns, and a 30-
night trial so you can test it out,
dream big, and wake up better. All
right, now let's go to our next story uh
about dead man walking.
>> This story gets even stranger.
Yesterday, two Republican senators, John
Thoon, John Baraso, both claimed they
had 20-minute phone calls with Kentucky
Senator Mitch McConnell, who's been in
the hospital for almost a month, Scott
Jennings. CNN, made the exact same
claim. And I think I just assumed, like
most normal people, that today we'd get
like a video from the senator from the
hospital thanking people for the
support, the prayers, and letting them
know that he's doing okay. But that
didn't happen. And the question is why?
Where is Mitch McConnell? What is going
on?
>> So, uh, Mitch McConnell might be brain
dead, but the press and the Republican
party are hiding it. Uh, and a bunch of,
uh, GOP senators and Scott Jennings are
obviously lying about it. [snorts] But
that was Newsmax host Rob Finery. Even
right-wingers are like, "No, this is
nonsense. Totally, utterly not true.
Where the hell is this guy?" Wait till
you find out why they're hiding this
condition. Anna, tell us more.
>> So, there are several
conservatives, Republicans who are
pretty furious about what's going on
here. And honestly, Jake, it's not that
shocking. Think about how furious
Democrats were. Uh, by the way, we were
also furious when it was abundantly
clear that Diane Feinsteight, a
Democratic senator, was in no condition
to remain in the Senate. She was
literally be being wheelchaired. um onto
the Senate floor by Nancy Pelos's
daughter. Uh she was suffering from, you
know, Alzheimer's. She was just in
really bad shape and we were upset
because we should have representation in
Congress and a senator who's unable to
represent us should not be in Congress.
So, with that in mind, uh let's go to
some of the other conservative
commentators and figures and hear what
they have to say. So, fellow Newsmax uh
host Carl Higgby says Republicans are
doing the same BS with McConnell that
Dems did with Biden. No one has actually
spoken to him. They are they are just
trying to carry this on to keep Thomas
Massie from running for his seat. And I
think there's a lot of truth behind
that. Now, uh there are other
Republicans speaking out. Let's just
quickly go to
let's go to Betty Johnson next video.
>> They're saying the exact same thing.
Here we go. I spoke with McConnell this
morning uh for just shy of 20 minutes
about Iran, Ukraine, and the unfolding
situation in Maine. Did you?
Uh
well, that seems to be also exactly what
other reporters are saying. John Thun
said McConnell and him spoke yesterday.
They had a lengthy and substantive
conversations on topics of national
security. Senate GOP leaders say they
spoken with Senator McConnell on the
phone for about 20 minutes and we talked
about Ukraine. Senator Baraso and
Senator McConnell had lengthy
conversation this afternoon. Their call
lasted roughly 20 minutes. It's just the
exact same thing. It's like a like a
template that they sent out. I don't
believe it.
I I just It's like, okay, if he's this
with it, then why not just have him do a
phone interview? He could call into this
program. Why doesn't if Mitch McConnell
called into CNN right now? If he's this
cogent and this sharp, just have him
call into CNN.
>> So, that's Benny Johnson. Uh he gets the
hunch. Uh obviously, the individuals who
claim that they've been speaking with
the senator um are lying. Uh Glenn Beck
is another person who's demanding
evidence. Let's take a quick look at
that.
>> I had a 20-minute conversation with uh
Mitch McConnell last night.
No, I didn't. No, I didn't. Okay. No, I
didn't. Cuz I could have a conversation.
I had a great 20-minute conversation
with Joe Biden yesterday. And you know
what it was?
And you you're wearing shoes today.
That's nice. Your shoes.
I'm wearing shoes today. You can have a
20-minute conversation with Joe Biden.
You can have a 20-minute conversation
with uh uh Mitch McConnell. But when did
the GOP become the same people that
we've been complaining about? Do you not
remember what we've been saying for the
last 5 years about people like, "I just
talked to Joe Biden. He's great and now
you're doing it. What's wrong with you?"
>> Apparently, uh, some on the right are
starting to realize that we live under a
party. Uh, but let's get to what Ken
Clippenstein is reporting. He says under
Kentucky law, if McConnell is declared
unfit for office before August 3rd,
there's a special election to fill out
his term. After that date, the seat sits
empty until whoever wins November's
already scheduled race is sworn in on
January 3rd. So, a longtime Capitol Hill
source told Ken um that congressional
Republicans don't want to risk a special
election, fearing GOP voters might
nominate a MAGA candidate over someone
friendlier to their party establishment.
Now, right now, MAGA has become the
party establishment, right? Because
Trump has totally pivoted to
neoonservative traditional Republican
garbage without actually being a
conservative. But nonetheless, fewer
than 5% of patients McConnell's age
survive an outofh hospital cardiac
arrest and most survivors suffer lasting
brain damage. And you know, in in regard
to those who are calling for some proof,
some investigations just to figure out
what's going on, you literally have the
governor of Kentucky, Andy Basher,
issuing the following statement. As
governor and a fellow public official
who understands the commitment we've
made to the people we serve, I am
requesting the senator provide an update
on his current health status. Allowing
speculation to continue in the media is
not fair to the senator or to Kuckians
and my hope is that this provides him
the opportunity to share the information
in a transparent manner direct from the
source. I wish him a safe and speedy
recovery. But, you know, I look, on one
hand, Jen, I get the fury because we
felt it ourselves when it came to Biden,
when it came to Diane Feinstein, but I
wasn't fully blackpilled when I felt
that fury. Uh, and now I am. And now I
see Congress for what it is, which is a
giant waste of our time and resources.
They get nothing done. They're totally
useless. The only thing they do is
constantly put their stamp of approval
on pork for their donors. And usually
that's in the form of defense
contractors, pharmaceutical companies,
and oil companies. But and Israel, of
course. But aside from that, what what
what have they done for us? When was the
last time Congress legitimately did
something that significantly benefited
the lives of ordinary Americans?
>> Yeah. Well, I was so blackpilled against
Joe Biden that I ran against him. I was
like, this is insane. He's not
functional. He's obviously scenile. And
everybody's like, "Oh, you're trying to
help Donald Trump." Like, "Uh, no. I'd
like someone with a brain so that they
could beat Donald Trump." No, no, we
don't want to beat Donald. Why don't you
want to beat Donald Trump? Oh, no. We
supporting the scenile guy. It's absurd.
It's absurd. By the way, good people
believe that. Why do they believe that?
Because our entire system is get you is
structured to get you to bow your head
to the powerful. So, if you're, you
know, if
Biden or Diane Feinstein is scenile, uh,
or has dementia on the on the Democratic
side, shut up. Don't ask any questions.
Well, who's the president? Who's
actually running the country? Who is the
governor? Who is the senator from
California right now? Who's the senator
from from Kentucky? Because it isn't
Mitch McConnell.
Mitch McConnell is not voting. He's not
making any decisions. uh these same
20inut conversations are such obvious
propaganda. By the way, let's note for
the record that that the people that say
that they had the conversations with
Mitch McConnell are enormous supporters
of Israel. Now, you say, "Wait a minute,
Jen. Why is that relevant in this
story?" Well, if they have a special
election, Tom Massie runs. He's from
Kentucky. They don't want that at all.
Even if it's symbolic, even if it's for
a small period of time, they're like,
"No, no." And besides which, who are all
the senators anyway? They apparently
don't make any decisions. That's why
when Feinstein or McConnell are
incapacitated,
nothing changes. Whoever's actually in
charge of their office puts out the same
policies that they would otherwise does
the same exact things. And Feinstein was
wheeled around and McConnell was for a
while too. They and then you saw with
your own eyes McConnell would freeze up
every once in a while. He kept falling
over and getting concussed all the way
back to 2023. And they just keep
wheeling them around and go, "Okay,
press this one McConnell. Press this for
Israel Feinstein. Press this for big
pharma. Press this for big oil and
defense contractors." So these our
senators and representatives are
widgets.
They're they don't they're not
independent decision makers. They're
very lowly servants for the donor class.
That's why when they are, even if
they're brain dead, the donor goes, "Who
cares?" That's even better for us. We
don't want them thinking on their own,
we want them to follow their godamn
orders. And whether it's Mitch McConnell
or his, you know, that works for
him, you know, that's his chief of staff
or whatever, press the goddamn button.
Shut up and do as the donors tell you.
And now McConnell goes, "Okay, if he's
still alive." I mean, it's they're make
Anna. They're turning our democracy. The
people who, oh my god, I'm so worried
about Trump. I'm worried about
democracy. I was worried about Trump.
That's why I did what I did. But don't
tell me you're worried about democracy
and you think it's no big deal that a
senator that is not functional is still
pretending to be functional, then you
don't care about our democracy and you
know their widgets. You know their
waiters and waitresses for the rich and
the powerful that have completely bought
our Congress. So, this is just a they've
turned it into a sick force. And in
moments like this, they start to rub it
in our face. Haha. You have no
representatives. You have no democracy.
All you have is a bunch of wealthy
people who bought all of Congress and
who bought all the media to tell you,
"Oh, yeah. This is not a play. No,
you're not at the theater. No, no, no.
This is real life. They are having
debates. They have different ideologies
and principles.
>> [snorts]
>> The whole thing's a goddamn joke.
>> I agree. All right, we got to take a
break. Let's do that. When we come back,
we'll uh discuss some other news,
including Marco Rubio, who is enabling
terrorists as we speak, uh arguing that
uh there needs to be an international
effort to go after Antifa. We'll be
right back.
[music]
>> [music]
>> All right. Uh, so Brother Tube writes
in, uh, on tyt.com, "No Anna for a week.
That sucks." I agree, but we try to do
the best we can. So, uh, we're going to
have a really interesting and eclectic
mix for you guys next week as guest
hosts. Adam Mockler is going to be on
Wednesday on Wednesday. Dave Smith's
going to be on Tuesday and Marjorie
Taylor Green is going to guest host on
Monday. So, wild week up ahead and
should be a lot of interesting
conversations filled with agreements and
disagreements and that is normal.
Cabbage writes in a agent Chuck Weaguer.
That's how uh uh John Kuryaku was
understandably mispronouncing my name.
And by the way, I I've mispronounced his
name many times. Angie Lynn says we
should believe the victim until or
unless an investigation proves
otherwise. Angie, I love you and I get
that a lot of people think that way, but
I don't agree. Uh and so
we don't know if they're a victim until
we know whether it's true or not.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, we're going to just
assume people are guilty and they have
to prove that they're innocent. So, just
understand what you're normalizing.
You're normalizing people, bad people's
ability to just make things up, to
destroy someone, whether it's in their
career, politics, whatever. And the onus
is on them to prove that they're
innocent. I don't want to live in a
system like that. I think that's a
really bad system. So, that's just my
take.
>> Angie and others, like, I get it. If it
happened, you're super pissed about it
and you've got every right, but we don't
know if it happened. That's the
question. By the way, we have this
question up on tt.com and on YouTube
community. Was it the right decision or
should he have stayed in the race? Uh,
vote if you can.
[music]
>> [music]
>> All right, back on TYT Jen and Anna with
you guys. Anna, which story you want to
do next? Uh, let's I I'm in a really bad
mood, so let's do the Marsha Blackburn
thing. Maybe it'll cheer me up.
>> Okay, that sounds fun. All right, let's
go to that now.
>> How hard am I going to crack [music]
down on China? Well, here's a clue.
>> Marsha Blackburn worked with President
Trump to take on communist China.
[music] As governor, Marsha will fight
to protect Tennessee land from Chinese
front companies, close loopholes, and
hunt down every communist who tries to
defy us. [music] It doesn't take a
fortune cookie to figure it out here in
Tennessee. We're going to stop communist
China and protect Tennessee land.
>> While that might look like a Saturday
night live skit, it isn't. That's a real
United States Senator, Marshall
Blackburn from Tennessee, and that's a
real ad.
Okay, so there are so many
inconsistencies and problems with that
ad that it is absolutely hilarious. But
the first one I'll point out, Anna, is
so we hate the Chinese communists and
their fortune cookies. And look, the
fortune cookie says that Marshall
Blackburn's right. So wait, do we hate
the fortune cookies or do we love the
fortune cookies?
>> That ad
was awesome. Okay, that [laughter] was
the best political ad I've seen in a
long time. Look, we need a little bit of
comedic relief in life. Okay, politics
has gotten too serious and I've been
waiting for someone left or right, who
cares? But you know that a bozo is going
to come out with a super embarrassing
ad. Like one of my favorite political
ads of all time was Senator Kennedy
coming out with that ad where he was
going after the BLM protesters and he's
like, "Oh, you need the cops? Well, call
a crackhead." Oh my god, that ad was so
funny. So obviously I don't agree with
his take, right? Because he's trying to
make a point about um how Black Lives
Matter like didn't whatever he
exaggerated what Black Lives Matter was
advocating for at the time, but it was
such a funny ad that I loved it and I
watched it over and over again. This is
the same taste, right? Ignorant woman.
You even hear like the stereotypical
music in the background. I don't
understand the need to crush the fortune
cookies. Like, aren't fortune cookies an
American creation?
>> Yeah. So, all right, let's break that
down. So, fortune cookies were uh
invented by a Japanese American uh
around I think 1907, if I remember
right. Um
>> Oh, that's amazing.
>> Yeah. And uh has nothing to do with
China. There are no fortune cookies in
China. Uh but again, she's like, "Ah,
it's so mad at the fortune cookies."
crumbles them and then like a positive
message about Marshall Blackburn comes
out of the cookie. So wait, are we
supposed to like and trust the cookie
that tells us that we should elect you
or are we supposed to hate the communist
cookie who actually is a communist and
isn't a person and is actually Japanese
American? Okay. By the way, also they
have soy sauce on the table. I know that
there's some Chinese brands of soy
sauce, but soy sauce is mainly Japanese,
not Chinese. Um
>> Oh, I didn't know that. That's actually
good knowledge uh to know. No, but I
let's also just quickly address the
elephant in the room. Uh, is war with
China something that's like making
voters cream in their pants? Like, is
that what they're looking for right now?
I don't know. I don't really get it.
>> No.
>> Like, is that what we're looking for? Go
ahead.
>> So, let me show you the foreign
government you should be concerned
about. Let's take a look at uh who
Senator Blackburn has received
contributions from. I know you're going
to be shocked. Oh, look at that. Israel,
$449,000.
She's now running for governor of
Tennessee. So, the problem isn't the
country who has a lobby that has given
to 94% of Congress, including Marshia
Blackburn. No, no, no, no. The country
that has forced us into seven wars that
has cost us $8 trillion. The country
that we've given $320 billion to, that
we're thinking of merging our militaries
with, that's not the country you should
be concerned about. squirrel, Chinese
squirrel. Look at the communist squirrel
and and the dastardly fortune cookie
they have. So, she thinks my voters are
generally racist. I want them to hate a
foreign country, but not beloved Israel.
I want them to love Israel because we
all serve Israel and I want to distract
them from that. So, COMMUNIST FORTUNE
COOKIE SQUIRREL, everybody get angry at
the Chinese.
>> So, here's the thing to understand,
though. uh for because there are people
in the country who desperately wanted
that pivot to Asia which kind of started
under Obama but we got sucked right back
into the Middle East our if you
genuinely think that we need to be
concerned about China and China is
spanking us right be partly we're
spanking ourselves China is growing in
power they are ascendant we are
declining in power and a big Reason why
is because we are basically blowing our
load, meaning our all our military
weaponry, our resources. We're $40
trillion in debt. We keep getting sucked
into Israel's wars in the Middle East
when I thought we were going to try to
stop doing that. But, you know, we we
can't. God forbid we actually start
looking out for the American people,
doing what's necessary to be competitive
on the global stage. All that money that
we've been spending on Israel's wars, we
could have actually utilized in research
and development here in the United
States, investing in our youth,
investing in, you know, the trade so
young people can have an option outside
of four-year institutions where they
take out an insane amount of debt and
will likely have the jobs that they're
getting degrees for replaced by robots
and AI. Like, I just you can't have
those two things. You understand? Like
you can't on one hand fearmonger about
China and how we need to focus on
fighting China while also simultaneously
being supportive of anything and
everything Israel wants. The two things
don't vibe if you get what I'm saying.
You can only have one and we've made our
decision to the detriment of our
country.
>> To your point, Anna, so the Chinese are
in an economic competition with us and
that's definitely real and often times
they cheat around the edges. uh and you
can say not around the edges but on core
things they flood our markets. There's a
bunch of things we've talked about that
we should fight back against uh when it
comes to the Chinese government. But
wait, let's break it down in two other
layers though. So the Chinese are out
competing our businesses. That's why
they're dastardly communists.
So the Chinese government, you could be
mad at them, but they keep calling like
I'm communist, right? Well, how
communist are they if they have all
these businesses that are out competing
us fairly or unfairly, right? No, it's a
mixed economy at this point. So, it's
they throw in the communists as a way of
like getting you angrier and more
demagoguery. You could be plenty angry
at the ways that they cheat on the
economic issues without bringing the
extra demagoguery in. That doesn't make
any sense in this context. They And by
the way, if you want to say that it's
not a free country, that is definitely
true. And that is a legitimate way of uh
critiquing the Chinese government again
without bringing things that don't make
sense. But my the most important part is
Chinese restaurants are American. She's
in a presumably in a Chinese restaurant
in Tennessee. She's not in Shanghai or
Beijing. And if you know anything about
Chinese restaurants, they're probably
the most capitalist businesses in the
country. You you need food on Christmas,
trust me, the Chinese restaurant is
open. you need food on Fourth of July or
Thanksgiving or past hours, the Chinese
restaurant's open. You know why? Because
they're interested in making money.
>> Yeah, I totally agree. Uh so anyway, I
guess that did lighten the mood a little
bit. Uh but now let's turn to Marco
Rubio. Let's do Fblock because I want to
talk about how he's trying to solicit
help from 60 countries for something um
idiotic. Go ahead, Jake.
>> Yes. Um, so, uh, Marco Rubio and some of
the others in the administration,
interesting who they are, are now trying
to pressure foreign governments into
labeling Antifa a terrorist
organization. Wait, what? Antifa barely
exists here, let alone in foreign
nations. So, what are they actually
trying to do? That's really interesting.
Anna, tell us more.
So, the Washington Post put out this
report and I was fascinated by it
because when you take a step back and
you look at the behavior of the United
States government and what we're
involved in in the Middle East, what we
are empowering and emboldening and what
we have emboldened in the Middle East,
there's quite a bit of terrorism going
on, right? A lot of innocent people are
getting killed. But Marco Rubio is
soliciting the help of 60 countries
in order to fight what the Trump
administration views as a major peril.
The resurgence of transnational far-left
terrorism.
That is insane. That is insane. That is
You have no right and no leg to stand on
when it comes to the topic of terrorism.
you have been bombing fishing boats in
the Caribbean. Okay? Like what are we
doing here? But anyway, this invitation
that Marco Rubio sent to 60 different
countries included most European nations
uh the larger Latin American countries
and uh several Asian countries including
India, Indonesia and um Singapore. And
so he's asking to meet with them like
get together this international meeting
where they discuss like fighting back
against the scourge of left-wing
terrorism. So Trump designated Antifa as
a domestic terrorist organization last
year. And additionally, and this is the
part that really gets me jank, Trump's
foreign counterterrorisms are Sebastian
Gorka, who's foreign. Uh you can tell by
his voice. I have no problem with
foreigners, but how about foreigners
don't label Americans as terrorists as
they're working for, you know, the White
House? But anyway,
Sebastian Gorka has been pushing for the
use of the terrorism label against
Antifa to basically justify viciously
going after left-wingers
as if they're like al-Qaeda terrorists.
Oh, no, no, not al-Qaeda terrorists.
actually armed those people and invite
them to the White House and spray
perfume on them. Anyway, uh a linkage to
foreign terrorist groups can unlock
certain investigative tools such as
surveillance, said one US
counterterrorism official. And uh if you
guys can remember through an interview
that I had done with Ken Clippenstein,
his original reporting found that
Sebastian Gorka was also looking to
label certain conservative Republicans
as terrorists, including Tucker Carlson,
simply because he doesn't agree with
Tucker Carlson's views on Israel.
>> So that reporting was done by Ken
Clippenstein. I even interviewed him
about it. You guys should check that out
if you missed it. But some US officials
rightly are very worried about this
move. Why is that? Some Trump
administration officials fear that a
future Democratic administration could
use the tactic against conservative
activists. One administration official
said, quote, "The idea is you're setting
a precedent for a future Gavin Newsome
administration to turn these authorities
on conservatives," the official said. So
it turns out that there are still people
with some, you know, functioning brains
in government. So, I'm really happy to
see that because whoever this person is,
they are absolutely right. You should
never advocate for the dismantling of
rights for anyone because it will
boomerang right back to you. And people
who don't see that, people who don't
realize that are digging their own
graves. In fact, some US officials have
even declined to go to this event that
Marco Rubio is putting together.
Discomfort with the administration's
direction is such that at meetings of
national security officials from various
agencies, some intelligence analysts
have declined to brief on Antifa because
they do not regard Antifa as a serious
counterterrorism threat according to one
person familiar with the matter. And to
be clear, US law actually requires a
group to be foreign in order for them to
be labeled a terrorist organization.
Former State Department official Jason
um Blasins, who ran uh the designation
process for 10 years uh through 2018,
told the Washington Post that if it has
any significant domestic presence, it
cannot be designated foreign. meaning
Americans cannot be uh labeled as
terrorists by our own government. Now,
Marco Rubio's previous designation of
foreign Antifa groups um was also called
into question because as you mentioned
earlier, Jenk, Antifa is an American
thing, but what Marco Rubio is trying to
allude to is just left-wing groups in
other countries. And so, uh Rubio has
linked foreign groups uh to Antifa
before. Back in November, for instance,
Rubio designated four European-based
groups as terrorist organizations with
ties to Antifa, the State Department
released a fact sheet on the groups with
the names the agency is using for them.
At least one of the groups is not known
by the name of their she on the on the
sheet. Uh in their countries, none are
linked to anything called Antifa. And so
the groups according to uh the state
department include uh Antifa OST in
Germany, the informal uh anarchist
federation or the international
revolutionary front in Italy. Like if
Italy is having problems with any group
in their own country, like they'll
handle it. Like why are we having like
this international consortium getting
together in order to fight back against
left-wingers? And the country that's
setting this up is the one
enabling Israel to carry out how many
different wars? Ethnic cleansing in
Lebanon, genocide in Gaza. You want to
talk about terrorism? You want to talk
about terrorism? There was a Palestinian
man who wanted to do something nice for
the Palestinians who are in Gaza right
now. So, he organized like screens for
them to be able to watch the soccer
matches as part of, you know, the FIFA
matches that have been going on. Um,
Israel bombed his car and killed him.
>> Jesus Christ, man. Yeah. No, no, there's
real terrorists in the world for sure.
So, I'll come back to them. So, we're
trying to shut down Antifa in Germany.
You know, Antifa is short for
anti-fascist.
Why do we want pro-fascist groups in
Germany? That doesn't sound like a good
idea, does it? So, but in reality, of
course, these groups are microscopic and
including here. And we used to have
debates on the show uh and discussions
on the show about, you know, what's
worse, leftwing or right-wing terrorism.
And, you know, the proof is overwhelming
on the right-wing side. But does it
really matter, guys? both are in the
scope of crime in America tiny. Okay. So
why they they're obsessed about this
even though there's almost no leftwing
or right-wing terrorism. Tiny tiny
amounts uh over the span of the last 10
20 years, right? So why are they getting
all agitated about both sides? And Gorka
is the giveaway. So if you don't know,
Marco Rubio, Sebastian Gorka, and Steven
Miller, the three people in the
administration most in favor of this and
pushing this forward are all Israel
first. And Gorka is the giveaway because
of what Anna said that it goes, "Oh, we
by the way, we should also use it
against the rightwing against Tucker
Carlson,
i.e. against all opponents of Israel, a
foreign government. But we should call
people who are criticizing Israel,
Americans criticizing Israel inside this
country, terrorists now. And then we
should get all of our allies to call
them terrorists. Guys, the surveillance
state is coming. And what's and this is
how the game is played. So now when the
theoretical right-wing is in charge,
they're not right-wing, they're just
Republican cutouts for a foreign
government, they come in and they go,
"Oh, left-wing terrorist. Oh, make sure
you pass this law and you all
coordinated against these terrorists.
And then a Democrat, so-called Democrat,
wins. And then he goes, "Oh, you have to
get the right-wing terrorists and you
have make sure we coordinate." Oh, look
at that. All Americans are terrorists.
Now we're doing a surveillance state on
all of you. That's why, and by the way,
you know, I've called uh right-wingers
who did, you know, attacks against
innocent civilians here and it meets the
definition of terrorism. In this story,
we find out that, you know, if you're an
American citizen, there's a different
word for you and not terrorist. And you
know what? I had already withdrawn that
earlier. I'm double withdrawing it now.
You know why? Because it's a dangerous
thing to start calling one another
terrorists. It it it it's a slippery
slope because once you call someone a
terrorist, then the government goes,
"Well, I have every right to take away
all of their rights." No, you don't. No,
you don't. They're American citizens.
Whether they're on the right or the
left, if they're accused of doing
something terrible, they still have
their rights. We go through a process.
We go through justice. And if they've
done something terrible, then we bring
justice to them. Okay? But we don't
bring injustice. And we certainly don't
do it to American citizens on behalf of
another country. If you're worried about
actual terrorism, I mean, imagine people
killing innocent kids on purpose. What
vicious terrorists. Well, there's a
country that we funded that killed
23,000
innocent children in Gaza.
Disgusting terrorists. the worst
civilian kill ratio of any terrorist
group in the world. And that's the
Israeli Defense Forces. But those guys
go, "No, give me your money. I'm sending
it to those terrorists to murder 23,000
children. But you, if you defy Israel or
anyone in power, WE'RE GOING TO CALL YOU
A TERRORIST and take away all your
rights." So that's what this is about.
>> Yeah, I agree. I I just have one final
thing to say. I want to go back to the
Platiner thing because it's just on my
mind.
I I just don't understand like every
This is like one of the most unjust
things imaginable because if Platiner
had actually committed the crime that
he's accused of when you don't go to the
cops, then you're just allowing someone
who allegedly forcibly raped you to just
be out on the loose to do what? To do
that to other women. Like, how is that?
And then you hold on to that information
until a week before an important
electoral deadline.
I just I don't know. I just don't get
it. I really don't. None of this makes
sense to me. And the fact that people
don't see the red flags like blows me
away. It really does.
>> So I'm going to read more member
comments in the bonus episode. That's
just for the members. So hit the join
button below tyt.com/join to get the
bonus episodes. But I'm going to read
one right now from a YouTube member box.
He said, "If he raped that woman, he
needs to go to prison. But to boot him
out of running was too much in my
opinion. The whole dem Democratic
establishment got together in a circular
firing squad again.
>> Yep.
>> And and that's the point we're making.
If he's guilty, the consequences should
be worse. He should go to prison, right?
>> But if he's not judged guilty, why are
the Democrats taking out their own guy?
CUZ THEY'RE NOT DEMOCRATS. They don't
care about the Democrats. The
Republicans take out their own guys if
they're opposed to Israel, too. Tucker
Carlson can on and on, right? because
they're not Republicans or Democrats.
They're the donor class. And that's what
the whole uni party's about. The whole
thing's a lie. So, look, this again,
there's a head-on collision coming from
the populist, the American citizens that
that now realize we don't control our
own government and the establishment who
will never ever stop lying to you. They
will lie to you till the very end and
say no, you should be controlled by
others. All right, we'll be right back
with a great interview.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey.
Hey. Hey.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat. Heat. Heat.
Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
All
right, guys. This is a very important
interview because we got him. Uh we've
got the producer of a movie called The
Muslim Invasion of America, and he's in
the studio, and he's going to tell us
all about this invasion that's coming
up. He was in the movie himself as well.
It's Beck Lover. Beck, how you doing?
>> Jen, thanks for having me. Huge fan of
you and Anna. And especially in these
recent times, how you guys are trying to
build bridges between right and left
because I think what's happening in the
world right now, it's going to take
everybody to come together to stop the
threat that I feel to all of our
freedom. And I think a lot of us are on
the same wavelength right now. So, I'm
very honored to be here today.
>> Thank you, brother. And you're Albania.
We'll talk about the Kushner takeover of
Albania. We'll talk about the Balkans a
little bit, but you know, I hear uh that
there's a Muslim invasion like in your
movie and that you know, Sharia law is
about to take over Tulsa, Oklahoma, and
parts of Texas,
>> Minnesota.
>> Okay. So, tell me about it.
>> All right, Jake. First and foremost, uh
I'm a first generation Albanian
American. I was born here because my
family fought against communism in
Albania. That's how I ended up here. My
dad had to leave the former Yugoslavia
because the oppression started there. So
I'm the direct son of two American, you
know, two Albanian immigrants. Uh
happened to be of the Muslim faith. I
came from a you know uh that background.
Uh I was in the World Trade Center the
day it was hit. Okay. I was going to
Pace University. I was a student there.
It's stones throw away. I actually
started my day in the era underneath
[snorts] the Burning Towers. I as a
Muslim American cried that day. I, as a
Muslim American, bled out that day. My
family, who's Muslim, even right now, is
serving in the US Navy. My cousin Brian
from Dallas, I won't say his last name.
My cousin Brian, who did two tours in
Fallujah, is a Muslim. Is he not an
American? He lost half of his battalion
there. So, the reason we made this film
is cuz these characters keep popping up.
the Valentina Gomezes, the Jake Langs,
the Laura Loomer, who I've didn't know
who she was ever in my life. Uh I call
her Jigsaw. I think a lot of the
internet does. I don't know if that's,
you know, acceptable on the show, but
>> it it just happened.
>> Uh yeah. So, so that's what I call her.
>> You know, I was someone that grew up
with Russian Jews. My family, my
grandmother's two brothers were hung by
the SS in northern Albania. Albania was
first under the Italian fascists under
Mussolini and then the Germans took
over. My two great uncles were hung off
trees. My first cousins are Jewish.
That's got to put out the card there
just in case they want to call me
something that I'm not. But I don't
think Jake Lang represents Christianity.
I would even question if he's a
Christian. We've all seen him here and
there in video clips and he's in Texas.
Now they said they banned him from the
state of Texas. He's been going to
places like Dearbornne where there is a
large, you know, Arab community, places
like Plano where there's a very
decentsized, you know, I would say more
Pakistani and some Arab uh, you know,
people that live there. You know, and I
know as an American, I've been
throughout this country from coast to
coast. I've driven all over it. There's
enclaves everywhere in America. If you
go to the Bronx, you're going to find
the Albanians. That's kind of like our
staging ground when we first landed
here. you know, anywhere you go
throughout the country, even in Plano,
the place that Jay kept going back to to
spew anti-muslim rhetoric that if anyone
else said about any other faith, they'd
be probably in jail, censored, uh you
know, their career destroyed, their life
destroyed. So, me and my my good friend
and partner, Sunonny Faz, who's a revert
to Islam. He just became a Muslim two
years ago. He's Italian. He chose this
faith. No one put a gun to his head. He
saw something in it that brought him
peace in his life and early on just as a
you know someone that's new to the faith
the amount of you know attacks he's
gotten in his life even from people very
close to him because of all this
propaganda that's gone on for the last
50 60 years against the faith of of
Islam which is you know 1/5if of the
world and we just celebrated our 250th
anniversary and a lot of Americans
forget that the first country to
recognize our independence as Americans
was a Muslim country which happens to be
Morocco which I their plane today, I
guess.
>> Yeah, they just lost to France. Yeah.
>> Oh, I didn't know. I don't, you know,
I'm trying to keep up. I'm trying to
save the world, Chank.
>> So,
>> so you know, and then, you know, and we
and they gave a port, right? Imagine if
we didn't have that first port as a new
nation. It was like a way of someone
giving a stamp and saying, "We we
recognize you as a country." So,
[snorts] hearing all these lies for
years, I never wanted to talk about
these things, Jen. I never went into
content or podcasting to speak about
religion or history or I never wanted to
talk about it because I knew first of
all the amount of backlash you get
because people just hate and then I also
knew you know in today's day and world
you're probably risking your life right
so you know you guys are in danger
>> just for speaking your mind so free
speech is never free it comes with a
risk or as Bosam Ysef says great friend
he's been here many times it comes with
terms and conditions so this film
does not have a script. It's not a film.
It's a documentary. We literally on a
very low budget took the two cameras.
All we had set up was meeting with the
two mayors of Dearborn and Dearborn
Heights. We didn't even know we would
run into Jake Lang. We thought we missed
him cuz we had went after he went to
Dearbornne and we're [snorts] like,
let's go see the Sharia takeover, you
know, this propaganda that they're
pushing, which I think any idiot by now
can figure out, you know, why they would
push this type of rhetoric. By the time
Muslims would ever be a perceived threat
in America, there's not enough Muslims
in America. First of all, we got bigger
problems like our deficit, like uh
inflation, like the fact that I went to
the supermarket and I look and
everything is just shrinking. The bag
looks the same, but there's less and
less items inside these same bags. They
think we're stupid. We're in [snorts]
serious trouble. So, I think the average
American should be focusing on our
politicians with their unlimited terms,
with their lobbying, which should be
made illegal. It's not really hard to
fix America. Make lobbying illegal.
Period. Term limits for Senate and
Congress. Period. No matter what, this
country should be protesting the way the
Albanians are protesting. Yet, we don't
have justice for many things, just as
everyday Americans. So, we need these
distractions. We made the film. It's
free. We didn't make it for money. And
it's called the uh the Muslim invasion
of America. You can type it on Google.
Go see for yourself.
>> Yeah.
>> What it is. So before I go go back to
that, I'm just curious. Where'd you grow
up in America?
>> So I was actually, my story is funny. I
was born in Houston. Didn't grow up
there. Thank God. No offense to Houston,
but humidity kills me, man.
>> Grew up in the New York City area.
Mostly on mostly on the Jersey side of
the Hudson.
>> I knew it.
>> Hoboken Edgewater.
>> You got Jersey, New York, Ren.
>> Jersey by close by.
>> East Brunswick. Yeah.
>> Okay. You're not far.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And we I we had a lot of
fun.
>> Summers in Kate May, you know, swimming.
That's where I learned how to swim in
Cape May, Jersey. But yeah, you know, I
spent a lot of time in the Bronx, too.
So, it's a very big hub for for our
people. Yeah. So, now back to to what
we're talking about. So,
there's this like propaganda about, oh
my god, Sharia law is about to take
over. That's why I was joking around
about it. Like, there's like I don't
know if there's three Muslims in
Oklahoma, right? Like, what are we
taking over?
>> You want my opinion? They could have it,
bro. Like, I've driven to Oklahoma.
Like, I'm terrified of tornadoes. me
personally
>> like uh I was about to settle in Dallas
and we went there and like in May I was
like you know I did like a temporary
residence to see if I want to set up
shop there
>> every two minutes like a warning tornado
I'm like listen let them have it I guess
but but my point is Jenk it's it's just
first of all just so Americans know like
please study the religion like go study
it go actually study read read a book
for once in your life Sharia law do you
know what one of the the the rules of
Sharia is
>> mm from the prophet Muhammad's mouth
himself peace be upon him when you live
in a foreign nation you must obey the
rules regulation and laws and the ruler
of that nation that is literally Sharia
law that means if you come from a Muslim
country and you live in the United
States of America you must live by its
constitution by its state laws federal
laws and whatever the president says but
fortunately we live in a country
supposedly that we have a right to push
back because it's supposed to represent
all of us I would rather much some of
these people say that believe this type
of rhetoric. I don't believe in freedom
of speech. Just say it. If you hate
Muslims, man, just say it. Just say you
don't want this to be an America that
gives everyone a shot. Muslims have been
here since day one. Chank.
>> So, but here's my question though, Beck.
Uh, so, and it's a there's so many like
great points there. So, I didn't know
about Morocco being the first country,
that's my bad, uh, to recognize America
>> and give them a port.
>> Yeah.
>> And it's still the longest alliance we
have in history. and uh Sharia law
saying you got to follow the rules of
the
>> the prophet's [clears throat] mouth.
>> No one knows that here in America. Okay.
So, but what they know is the
propaganda. So, my question is where
because since that propaganda is so
absurd like the idea that Muslims are
going to take over Texas, right? Where
is it coming from?
>> In my opinion, lobbyists, paid
influencers, people that support the
policies and the endless wars that have
taken us into a a a disaster in the
United States of America. this endless
cycle of war in the Middle East. Uh I
would have to agree it definitely
benefits Israel, right? And you know to
me it's like you know you you got to
dehumanize people brother if you can do
but what I don't understand and maybe
they should pay attention. It would have
been smarter for Israel to have only
gone over go after dehumanizing the
Arabs. I I don't understand why they
went after the whole religion. We are a
world faith of two billion people. We
come in every shape, size, and color. I
am from Europe. I am considered what you
would call white. The minority of
Muslims are Arabs. They're only 19%. Why
did they go after the whole faith with
their propaganda? It makes no sense to
me. And it's very offensive as someone
whose family was killed by the Nazis.
When you study basic history, check, you
study the caliphate. People like
throwing that word around. They're
trying to start another caliphate. Why
don't you guys go study the first two
[snorts] and read about the life of Omar
al-Katab only 6 years after the life of
the prophet Muhammad when he got control
of Jerusalem. [snorts] The Jews were not
allowed to live in Jerusalem for 500
years. Jenk, this is not something Beck
is saying. This is common sense history.
You can go look it up yourself. Even in
their own books, in their own history,
their own historians wrote about these
experiences.
For 500 years, they couldn't step foot
in that city. And the first action of
the Muslim ruler was how come there are
no Israelites, no Jews at this time,
sir? They were wiped out. They were
pushed out. They weren't allowed to
return. For 500 years, the first action
of the Muslims was to say, "Bring me 80
families and resettle them immediately."
Throughout history, they were protected.
If you actually look at the history of
Muslims and Jews, yet I got to sit back
here and listen to someone like Laura
Loomer and listen to people like Randy
Fine and listen to people who push
things that are historically completely
fabricated, completely uh you want to
talk about being an extremist and now
you're dehumanizing a faith, a world
faith that's brought so much peace to
me. But the most disrespectful part of
it all, Jenk, the religion that in my
opinion, if it didn't exist, I don't
think they would exist either. I don't
think they would have survived the
Inquisition and the Holocaust. The only
country that saved all of its Jews
during the Holocaust was the same
country that my two great uncles were
hung off trees in northern Albania, and
Tropoa to be exact. 16 and 18 years old,
not a single Jewish refugee during World
War II, died in Albania. And to be fair
to my people, they're all, you know,
we're Muslim, Christian, Orthodox. We've
never fought over war. There was all
three religions involved in saving them,
but predominantly Muslim. That's why
Jenk, you never saw a movie once in
Hollywood. Where are you, my brothers
and sisters? I have so many friends that
are Jewish. Where's the film about the
only country that saved you in World War
II? Do you know why you never saw a film
about Albania saving the Jews? You've
seen movies about everything you can
imagine in World War II.
Why did they never make a movie about
Albania? because they don't even want to
show slightly any positivity between
Muslims and Jews. That's why that film
was never made.
>> So uh I'll go a little further. I'll
list a bunch of things then ask you a
question. So first of based on the
things you said. Number one u the Turks
saved hundreds of thousands of Jews from
the uh Inquisition in Spain.
>> That that's a fact. They followed them
once they were kicked out of you know
the Muslims were kicked out of Andalusia
which was an enlightenment a gold period
in history. So while the Christians, you
know, and look, it's not today's
Christians fault, but it was just a
fact. Yeah. When the Catholics were
slaughtering uh the Jews in in Spain,
the Ottoman Empire pulled up his entire
navy and said, "Give them all to us and
save them all." Okay. So the idea that
Muslims hate Jews is just ahistorical.
It's just not remotely true.
>> And not just that, during that empire,
they were allowed to have their own
court systems under the they had
basically self-ruule within the Muslim
Empire.
>> Yeah. And then you know uh to your point
about
why did they decide to demonize all the
Muslims like you never like the number
the biggest Muslim country in the world
is Indonesia.
>> There was never a war there.
>> There was never a jihad.
>> Yeah. And none of the top four Muslim
countries are Arab. Okay. That's uh
Pakistan. It's Indonesia first and
Pakistan, India, uh Nigeria, etc. Right.
So then you got Turks, you got the
Iranians that are also not Arabs. So my
guess as to why that happened, Beck, is
because if you say that Arabs are
terrorists by nature, you're an obvious
racist, right? Because it's a race that
you're attacking and there's no basis
for it. But if you say Muslims believe
because of their belief system, their
religion in fighting against Jews or
Christians, it makes it sound more
believable.
>> But it's not even accurate. It's not
accurate. And they say global war on
terror. Wait, was it global?
>> No, it was against Israel's neighbors.
>> Correct.
>> So all of this, in my opinion, is
propaganda started by Israel so that
America will hate Muslims so that we'll
pay and finance for Israel's wars
against their Muslim neighbors.
>> I would have to agree with that. Yeah, I
would have to agree with that. You know,
and another thing is, you know, Spain,
it wasn't called Spain, it was the Goth
Kingdom, was controlled by the Moors for
500 years. I always thought the Muslims
invaded. I was like, why would they
invade? Like, I never knew the history.
They were having a civil war, the Goth
Kingdom, and [snorts] half of them
didn't recognize the the one that was
put in power. So, they invited the Moors
to come in. The Moors took over. They
won. And then all three religions
practiced in peace. today. Is not Spain
still one of the most Catholic countries
in the world?
>> It is.
>> So when they say Islam was spread by the
sword, yet them as Christians don't look
in the mirror, and I'm not here to pick
on Christians, but this is they're in my
opinion, they're using Christians to
fight their wars. They have to pump them
full of hatred and then unleash them on
the Muslims because they're only 13
million. So how do I go against a couple
billion? Let me let me light both sides
of the fire and make them hate each
other.
>> Yeah. And again, look, we both have
Jewish family. It isn't the
>> extremist from their sides.
>> Yeah. It isn't the Jews doing it. It is
a very specific group, right? Like for
example, right now twothirds of Jewish
Americans are against the current
Netanyahu government in Israel those
stats two days a day ago, two days ago.
>> Only a third are in favor of Netanyahu.
But that third unfortunately has
billions upon billions upon billions of
dollars and they use it. They're radical
Zionists. Not the whole third even, but
there's radical Zionists in this country
who say, "No, you should despise
Muslims." By the way, we're so concerned
about bigotry when it comes to
anti-semitism. It's a total lie. It's
just another excuse to hide uh and and
shield Israel. Okay. Now, let's turn to
Albania where you're from. So, Albanians
have some fighting spirit. So, the
Kushner goes over there and Ivanka and
what are they doing? They're trying to
take over an island that's like a
basically a national treasure for
Albania. Tell me about it and how the
Albanians are pushing back.
>> Albanians have a very tragic history.
We're literally, you know, one of the
oldest, if not one of the oldest people
in all of Europe. And because we've
always been occupied by foreign powers,
the fact that we even survived is a
miracle. Okay? The fact that our
language is still intact. First under
the Romans, then the Ottoman Turks, then
under the Slavs, then communism came and
for the first time ever, Albanian
history is finally getting out there.
Albanians [snorts] are by far I want to
say this to the country to to the whole
world. Albanians are the most
pro-American people on the face of the
planet. This is not a protest or a push
back against America. This is a push
back against corruption and backdoor
deals that are done through oligarchs
and prime ministers and people doing
favors for each other. And we have these
problems within our own country. I just
wish as a first generation Albanian
American, my fellow Americans would wake
up to the type of corruption we have in
our country because I used to think we
were really good until I I you was naive
as a young person. And I used to believe
the movies and the president would you
know they would show that in the movie
the president there's a tsunami coming
no I'm going to stay in the white house
when he can get away like so you know so
for me what happened over there people
communism took over my family that's
where I was born my family were
anti-communist fighters my
great-grandfather was thrown into a
gulag for 28 or 29 years how he survived
miraculous never got to meet him he died
two years shortly my great-grandmother
was hung by the Albanian communist Under
the regime of Enberhoja, the state in
communism takes all the land. They put
whoever was dissident into what was
called interimi or interment camps. My
mom's first cousins all grew up in those
camps and they take your land and then
give to, you know, resettle people. So
for a couple two generations, people
lost their land and other people lived
on their land and then communism fell.
But now I've been here for two
generations, but it's my family's land
before communism. Cuba is going to have
the same problem when it falls. And
instead of settling these land disputes
which have really hurt the Albanian
people and created problems and violence
and stuff like that, our the prime
minister there figured out a way to give
away. So we can't figure out they can't
figure out for their own citizens how to
give them back their land before
communism, but they could figure out how
to give away one of the most precious
pieces of property that the Albanians
have. It's not a large country, okay?
They don't have many islands. And I, as
an American, I've been to Puerto Rico,
Aruba, I've been to all these beautiful
places. The local population doesn't
flourish just because you build a
five-star resort. Okay? What happens is
they can't even access that beachfront.
They can't go there on vacation. If he
really cared about his country, if Eddie
Rama did in the Flamingo Revolution, cuz
even I forgot as an Albanian, we have
flamingos there. That's how beautiful
this place is. mountains, crystal clear
water, a very hospitable people that
even names its streets after American
presidents because Albania survived the
collapse of the Ottoman Empire thanks to
Woodro Wilson going to bat for them
because we did lose about 80% of our
territory, the Albanian people. So, they
got to keep that little peace otherwise
we would have been like the Kurds, a
nation without a home. And that is why
the Albanians honor America. They love
them. It was unfortunate that the
Albanians fell behind the Iron Curtain,
but [snorts] you have literally they
even named a highway from Kosovo to
Albania called Bo Biden Highway. Again,
they don't understand Republican,
Democrat, you know, all the stuff that's
been happening in our country. The
Albanian people just want to honor and
remember America, but what bothers me is
Israel, and I lost, remember, my
father's side is from Kosovo, and Kosovo
had a very bloody conflict. It wasn't as
bad as the Bosians, but it was really
bad. Two million people were made
refugees overnight. The Clinton
administration
initiated bombing with NATO which
liberated them from that disaster. And
[snorts] what a lot of people, you know,
try to twist is originally cuz a big
piece of the Albanians were pushed into
Yugoslavia. We're not Slavic. We're not
Slavic speaking. We've been there
forever. Our DNA is the most continuous
DNA. This is proven now. The most
continuous DNA in the Balkans.
Literally. So we were put into all these
different countries, right, and treated
like crap and under socialism and all
this stuff. And [snorts] the Albanians
were stripped of their autonomy in
Kosovo by Malloich and his regime. And
they weren't even asking for
independence at that time, Chen. They
just wanted their rights back that they
had under Tito of Yugoslavia.
>> Make the story short, that didn't work.
They tried civil disobedience for 20
years. It led to an armed rebellion. And
thankfully, America got involved.
Otherwise, we would have been just like
the Bosnians. They lost hundreds of
thousands of people. We lost an
estimated 20 to 30,000. There was a lot
of crimes committed there. But I lost 28
very close family, friends, uh, first
cousins, uncle, and it was very
dramatic, you know, as an American to,
you know, I used to go back there in the
summers and see what life was like under
occupation during the Mallich regime. So
when I say the Albanians love America,
we literally owe our existence to them.
>> Yeah.
>> So this protest is not against America,
I want to clarify this. The Albanians
are would never betray America. They
would be the first country to fight for
America. But what bothers me, Chen, is
why would our greatest ally, that's what
they call Israel. Yes.
>> NATO [snorts] is very important to the
US. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Why would Serbia and Israel do a weapons
deal about few months ago with Elbit
Systems for $1.6
billion? Drones is the future of war.
We've all seen the footage in Ukraine.
We've seen the footage everywhere of how
dangerous drone warfare is. That is the
future. It's not fighter jets. Okay. Why
would our greatest ally go to, and
again, I got nothing against the
Russians. Why would they go and do a
deal with Russia's greatest ally? How
does that work? Why are we giving them
money, billions of dollars, so that they
they can give Serbia the right to make
drones? Then you had Netanyahu go to
Republica Serpska, which is a very
volatile situation in Bosnia. My fear is
there is a conflict coming to the
Balkans because of the people Serbia has
been and I got to give them kudos, okay?
[snorts] They've been protesting since
before Albania against Vuch their their
prime minister because of the same
grievances. The Balkans has been poor,
used and abused for hundreds of years by
the powers that be. It's been the
crossroads. It's where World War I
started. Y
>> and I am scared that they are setting
the primes and getting ready to light
the match of the the number one powder
keg in the world, the Balkans. It does
not benefit the youth. I think a lot of
the youth are up, you know, even though
they had traditional rivalries, Serbs,
Albanians, Croats. I say this message to
the people of the Balkans. Do not take
the bait of these that want to
radicalize and try to use old conflicts
to make us kill each other so they can
keep their puppets in power. That's my
fear, Jen. Yeah, I I want to build on
that. So, I've said on the show before,
you know, Muslims in southeastern Europe
in the Balkans are the most pro-American
people on the planet, right? Albanians,
Bosnians, Kosovo, Serban. So, why
America saved those Muslims from a
genocide, a lot of them, right?
>> I mean, with the Bosnians, they were, to
be honest, I feel like they let the
Bosnians down. They placed an arms
embargo on them. That's when I became an
activist.
>> But then they came in at the end
>> at the end and stopped it. But it was
pretty bad. Jen,
>> I know. I know. But still, they saved
>> and they carved their country up like a
Turkey and they barely gave them any
coast. I mean, I don't think that I
think the Bosians were dealt with very
unjustly in many ways. But, uh, I
understand what you're saying. They
would have kept on going forever until
they were wiped out.
>> Yeah. And so, we came in and saved them
at the end. Woodro Wilson sets up
Albania. We free all those folks from
communism. Right. So, super strong
pro-American sentiment in that region,
especially from the Muslims in that
region. They have statues of George Bush
in Albania. They have statues of Bill
Clinton. Do you understand? They don't
understand the politics. They're just
like, "These people, they saved us. We
love them." And this is even before the
Kosovo War. That's what I'm saying. I
don't want the Americans to think, "Oh,
they're pro." No, they're protesting
against the same reason we should be
protesting as America. Where is my money
going? He's trying to throw a concert
with Kanye West right now. $4 million
that people are like, "What do you mean?
He's building a stadium. He's already in
the worst uh scandal. I I have never
seen our people disunited. And they're
not just calling for the resignation of
the prime minister. They want the entire
government out.
>> We should do the same thing.
>> They want the entire government out.
America will never be what it needs to
be as long as we have unlimited term
limits and lobbying. We will never be
the nation that we could we could be the
we we could be the most amazing country
in the world. But this corruption is is
like gang green and there's no way out
without pain and we need to you know as
Americans we really need to wake up
right now. We need to put away this left
and right stuff for a while. We really
need to put away this left and right
stuff.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. And let's focus on what's going on
here because I don't think we're going
to celebrate another 250 years the way
we're going. I don't think we're going
to survive another 250 months the way
things are going. But Beg, last thing
here is we run short on time. So,
exactly on that point. Now, I see when I
talk to Armenians and Turks in the
streets in America, they they're like,
forget grievouses from the past, okay?
We totally agree on ending the genocide
in Gaza, right? I see Muslims and
Christians getting together. I see Jews,
too.
>> And and plenty of Jews have joined,
>> tons of Jews, yeah, on our side getting
together against genocide, against wars,
etc. I see right and left coming
together. Is is what Israel doing in
Albania and America and all these
places? Um and because let's keep it
real, Jared Kushner is totally connected
to the Israelis, right? And and so
>> he cares more about them than him.
>> Of course he does. Right. So is what
Israel doing accidentally uniting the
world? I would have to say it is. And I
feel for Jews, brother. I really do,
brother. I really, really do. Like I
said, I grew up in New York City. Half
my friends, half of Pace University was
like Russian Jews. But some of the best
people I've ever met in my life. I've
had some of the best nights of my life.
And I feel weird speaking about these
things because we've been preconditioned
that God forbid you say anything against
Israel, all of a sudden you hate. No, I
don't hate Jews. My family was willing
to die to save them. My people were
willing to die to save them. My first
cousins are Jews. My whole life I've
respected them. And many of their
articles of what they believe in in
their religion, I believe in. I'm
circumcised. I'm snipped. I don't eat
pork, you know. I technically if I can't
find halal, I'll eat kosher, right? So
much great respect for the faith. I my I
I can't I don't want to say my
children's names. Very common names in
their religion. So my point is this
narrative that Muslims and Jews are
enemies is a lie. A complete
fabrication. I'll debate here. I'm I
will debate anyone in the world on that
topic.
>> Yeah.
>> Have you had instances here and there?
Yeah. But I'm talking about overall
throughout history. Yeah. It's a lie.
>> No question about it. All right,
everybody check out Muslim Invasion of
America. Uh, it's an ironic title, of
course, about uh what's happening in
this country. Beck, anything else they
should check out? That's it. I mean, if
they want to check me out on, you know,
becklover.com, becklover.com or
becklovernyc
on Instagram. And I was yesterday with
Bone Thugs in Harmony as they received
their uh star of, you know, on [snorts]
the Walk of Fame. One of their members
is a Muslim. I guess he's a terrorist,
too. I mean, I don't know. He just, you
know, they won a Grammy. That's awesome.
All right, Beck, thanks for coming in.
Appreciate it. Pleasure.
>> All right, guys. I'm going to do a bonus
episode for the members next. I'll see
you in a minute.
[music]